trust us
우리를 신뢰
ok that works ok good we'll get started soon so today we'll be talking about the
확인 그것은 우리가 곧 그래서 오늘 우리가 얘기 할 수 있습니다 시작합니다 확인 좋은 작품
recurrent neural networks which is one of my favorite topics one of my favorite
내가 가장 좋아하는 주제 내 좋아하는 일 중 하나입니다 재발 성 신경 네트워크
models to play with input into neural networks just everywhere there a lot of
모델은 도처에 많이 신경 네트워크에 입력으로 재생
fun to play with in terms of administrative high temps recall that
재미 관리 높은 임시 직원의 관점에서 놀 리콜
your midterms on Wednesday this Wednesday you can tell that I'm really
수요일에 여러분의 중간 고사는이 수요일 당신은 정말이야 말할 수 있습니다
excited I know if you guys are excited very excited to me what a cemetery will
너희들은 나에게 매우 흥분 흥분하는 경우 내가 아는 흥분 무엇 묘지는 것
be out due this Wednesday it's so he will be out on Wednesday its due two
그렇게 그는이 그것 때문에 수요일에 밖으로있을 것이다 것이 수요일 인해 외출
weeks from now on Monday but I think since we're shifting it I think to
월요일에 지금부터 주 그러나 나는 우리가 그것을 이동하고 이후가 생각하는 생각
Wednesday we plan to have released it today but we're gonna be shipping it to
우리가 계획 수요일은 오늘 발표했다합니다 그러나 우리는거야에 출하 할 수있어
roughly Wednesday so we'll probably the first deadline for a few days and
대략 수요일 그래서 우리거야 아마 몇 일에 대한 첫 번째 마감일과
assignment to him of mistaken was due on Friday so if you're using 38 days then
그런 다음 삼십팔일를 사용하는 경우, 그래서 오해의 그에게 할당 금요일에 기인
you'd be having it in today hopefully not too many of you are doing that our
당신은 일을 당신의 너무 많은 희망을 갖고 오늘을 낳게 될 것입니다 우리의
people down with a 72 or many people are done okay most of you looking great for
72 또는 여러 사람과 사람 아래로는 대부분의 위대​​한 찾고 좋아 완료
doing well so currently in the class were talking about coming ashore neural
클래스에 너무 현재 잘하는 해변 신경오고에 대해 얘기했다
networks las Casas specifically we looked at to visualizing understanding
네트워크 라스 카사스는 특히 우리는 시각화 이해를 보았다
convolutional neural networks so we look at a whole bunch of pretty pictures and
길쌈 신경망 우리는 예쁜 그림의 모두 볼 수 있도록하고
video so we had a lot of fun trying to interpret exactly what he's accomplished
비디오는 그래서 우리는 많은 재미 그가 달성 정확히 어떤 해석을 시도했다
all networks are doing what they're learning how they're working and so on
모든 네트워크는 그들이 그렇게 작업하고있는 방법을 학습하는 일을하고 있습니다
and so we debug this through several ways that you may become a call from a
그래서 우리는 당신이에서 호출 될 수있는 몇 가지 방법을 통해이 문제를 디버깅
structure actually over the weekend I stumbled by some other visualizations
구조는 실제로 주말에 나는 다른 시각화에 의해 발견
are new I found these on Twitter and they look really cool and I'm not sure
내가 트위터에서 이러한 발견 새로운 그들은 정말 근사하고 잘 모르겠어요
how to how people made these because there's not too much description to it
어떻게 너무 많은 설명이 아니기 때문에 사람들이 만든 방법
but looks like this is turtles tarantula and then this is chained and some kind
이 거북 독 거미이고, 다음이 연결 및 어떤 종류처럼 만 보인다
of a dog and so the way you do this I think it's something like the tree nuts
이렇게 개 등 방식 나는 그것이 견과류 같은 생각
again optimization into images but they're using a different regularize on
다시 이미지로 최적화 그러나 그들은에서 다른 정례화를 사용하는
the image in this case I think they're using a bilateral filter which is this
이 경우 이미지가 나는 그들이이있는 양​​자 필터를 사용하고 생각
kind of a fancy filter so if you put that regularization on the image that my
멋진 필터의 종류는 해당 이미지에 해당 정규화를 넣어 그래서 만약 내
impression is that these are the kinds of visualizations that you achieve
느낌이 당신이 달성 시각화의 종류가 있다는 것입니다
instead so that looks pretty cool but I am not sure exactly what's going on I
대신에 꽤 멋진 보이지만 내가가는 정확히 무엇인지 확실하지 않다 그래서
guess we'll find out soon
우리는 곧 알게 될 같아요
ok so today we're going to be talking about recurrent neural networks what's
확인 그래서 오늘 우리는 재발 성 신경 네트워크 무엇의에 대해 얘기 할거야
nice about recurrent neural networks is that they offer a lot of flexibility in
재발 성 신경 네트워크에 대한 좋은들은 많은 유연성에 제공한다는 것입니다
how to wire up your network architectures
네트워크 아키텍처를 배선하는 방법
normally when you work with no let's hear the case on the very left here
더 작동하지 않을 때 보통의가 바로 여기 왼쪽에있는 경우를 들어 보자
where you are given a fixed size picture here in red then you process it with
당신이 빨간색으로 여기에 고정 된 크기의 사진을 제공하는 경우 당신은 그것을 처리
some hidden layers and green and then produce a fix I saw the better in San
녹색 다음 몇 가지 숨겨진 레이어 내가 산에 더 나은을보고 수정을 생산
image comes in which is a fix I statements and we're producing a fixed
이미지가 제공하는 수정 I 문이며 우리는 고정을 생산하고
size picture which is the closest course when the recurrent neural networks we
가장 가까운 코스가 크기 사진 때 재발 신경망 우리
can actually operate over sequences sequence at the input output or both at
실제로 입출력 또는 둘 모두에서에서 시퀀스 순서를 통해 작동 할 수 있습니다
the same time so for example in the case of image captioning and we'll see some
동시에 영상 자막의 경우 예를 들어, 우리가 일부를 볼 수 있도록
of it today you're given a fixed size image and then through a recurrent
그것을 오늘 당신은 반복을 통해 다음 고정 된 크기의 이미지를 부여하고
neural network we're going to produce a sequence of words that describe the
신경망 우리는를 설명하는 단어의 시퀀스를 생성하는 것
content of that image so that's going to be a sentence that is the caption for
그래서 그 이미지의 내용에 대한 캡션입니다 문장이 될 것
that and in the case of sentiment classification in the lobby for example
그 예를 들면 로비 감정 분류의 경우,
were consuming a number of words and sequins and they will try to class
단어와 장식 조각의 수를 소모하고, 그들은 클래스에 시도 할 것이다
driver the sentiment of that sentence is positive or negative in a case of
드라이버 그 문장의 감정의 경우 긍정적 또는 부정적
machine translation we can have a recurrent neural network that takes us a
기계 번역 우리는 우리 소요 재발 성 신경 네트워크를 가질 수있다
number of words in say English and then asked to produce a number of words in
다음 말 영어 단어의 수는 단어의 개수를 생성하라는
French translation so we'd feed this end Andrew recurrent neural network in what
프랑스어 번역 그래서 우리는이 말 앤드류 재발 성 신경 네트워크를 공급했던 것과
we call sequence to sequence kind of setup and so this work or not work with
우리는 설정의 순서 종류의 순서를 호출 등이 작업 여부는 작업
just performed translation on arbitrary sentences in English into French and in
단지 프랑스어와 영어에 임의의 문장에 대한 번역을 수행
the last case for example we have video classification where you might want to
당신이 할 수있는 경우, 예를 들어 지난 경우 우리는 비디오 분류를
imagine classifying every single frame of a video with some number of classes
클래스의 일부 번호와 비디오의 매 프레임을 분류하는 상상
but crucially don't want to the prediction to be only a function of the
하지만 결정적으로의 전용 함수로 예측 싶지 않아
current time step the current frame of the video but also all the things that
현재 시간은 모든 것을 비디오의 현재 프레임 단계하지만
have come before it in the video as a recurrent neural networks allow you to
재발 성 신경 네트워크가 당신을 허용하는 비디오에 전에왔다
wire up in architecture where the prediction that every single time step
건축 와이어 최대 위치를 예측하는 매 시간 단계
is a function of all the frames that have come in up to that point now even
지금까지도 그 지점까지 들어오는 모든 프레임의 함수이다
if you don't have sequences that input or output you can still use recurrent
만약 입력 또는 출력 여전히 재발을 사용할 수있는 서열을 가지고 있지 않다면
neural networks even in the case on the very left because you can process your
심지어 당신이 처리 할 수​​ 있기 때문에 매우 왼쪽에있는 경우 신경망 당신의
fix as inputs or outputs sequentially for example one of my favorite examples
예를 들어, 입력 또는 출력 순차적으로 내가 가장 좋아하는 예제 중 하나를 수정
of this is from people from deep mine for a while ago we're trying to
이 잠시 전에 우리가 노력하고 대한 깊은 광산에서 사람들된다
transcribe house numbers and instead of just having this big image feet into a
집 번호를 전사 단지에이 큰 이미지 발을 갖는 대신
comment and try to classify exactly what house numbers are in there they came up
의견 그들이 와서 집 번호가에 정확히 분류하는 시도
with a recurrent neural network policy where there's a small come that and it
작은 거기에 재발 신경 네트워크 정책과 그 와서
steered around the image especially with recurrent neural network and so their
특히 때문에 자신의 재발 성 신경 네트워크와 함께 이미지 주위 조향
current work learned to basically readout house numbers from left to right
왼쪽에서 오른쪽으로 현재 작업은 기본적으로 집 번호를 판독을 배운
sequentially and so we have pics as input but we're processing it
순차적 그래서 우리는 입력으로 사진을 가지고 있지만 우리는 그것을 처리하고
sequentially conversely we can think about this is also a well-known people
순차적으로 반대로 우리가 이것에 대해 생각할 수도 잘 알려진 사람이다
draw this is a general model what you're seeing here are samples from the model
이것은 당신이 모델에서 샘플을 여기서 볼 수 있습니다하는지 일반 모델 그리기
where it's coming up with these digits samples but crucially we're not just
이들 숫자 샘플과 함께오고 있지만 결정적으로 우리는 단지하지 않은 경우
predicting these digits at a single time but we have our current network and we
한 번에이 숫자를 예측하지만 우리는 우리의 현재 네트워크와 우리가
think of the up as a canvas and the kernel goes in and painted over time and
캔버스로까지 생각하고 커널에가는 시간이 지남에 그린과
so you're giving yourself more chance to actually do some computation before you
그래서 당신은 자신에게 실제로 전에 몇 가지 계산을 할 수있는 더 많은 기회를 제공하고 있습니다
actually produce you're out that it's more powerful kind of form of processing
실제로 당신이 처리 형태의 더 강력한 종류의 것을있어 생산
data was a question over the specifics of exactly what this means for now
데이터는이 지금은 무엇을 의미하는지 정확히의 특성을 통해 질문이었다
eros just indicated indicate functional dependence so things are so things are
일이 일이 너무 그래서 그냥 표시 에로스는 기능 의존도를 나타냅니다
harsh enough things before and we're going to exactly what that looks like in
거친만큼 일하기 전에 우리가가는 것을 정확하게 그처럼 보인다
a bit okay so these are generated house numbers so the network looked at a lot
네트워크가 많이 보았다 그래서이 너무 좋아 조금 집 번호를 생성
of house numbers and came up with a way of painting them and so these are not in
집 숫자와 이러한 그림의 방법으로 와서 그래서 이들에없는
a training day on these are made up numbers from the model none of these are
이들의 훈련 일이이의 모델 없음에서 숫자를 만들어
actually the training set these are made up
실제로 교육이 만들어집니다 세트
yeah they look quite real but they're actually made up from the local
그래, 그들은 아주 진짜 보이지만 그들은 실제로 현지에서 만든 것
so a recurrent neural network is basically this thing he remarks and
그래서 재발 성 신경 네트워크 그가 발언이 것은 기본적이며,
green and it has a state and it basically receives through time it
녹색 및 그 상태를 가지며, 그것은 기본적으로 시간을 통해 수신하고 그것을
receives an actress so every single time that we can feed in an input vector into
우리가에 입력 벡터에 공급 할 수있는 여배우 그래서 매번 수신
the armed men and it has some state internally and then it can modify that
무장 한 남자와 내부적으로 어떤 상태를 가지고 있으며, 다음은 그 수정할 수 있습니다
state as a function of what it what it receives every single time step and so
그것은 매 시간 단계를 받고 그래서 것의​​ 함수로서 상태
they're all of course be weights and CNN and so when we turn those wastes the
그들은 우리가 그 폐기물를 켤 때 물론 모든 무게와 CNN 등 수있어
Arnold different behavior in terms of how its stated goals as it received
명시된 목표는 수신 한 방법의 측면에서 아놀드 다른 동작
exempts I usually we can also be interested in producing and all but
나는 보통 우리는 또한 생산에 관심이있을 수 있습니다 면제 및 모든하지만,
based on the R&S state so we can produce these matters on top of the hour now but
우리가 지금 만 시간의 상단에 이러한 문제를 생성 할 수 있도록 R & S 상태에 따라
so you'll see a show pictures like this but I just like to know that the Arnon
그래서 당신은 이런 쇼 사진을 볼 수 있지만, 난 그냥 아르 논 것을 알고 싶다
is really just the block in the middle
정말 블록은 중간에
worked as a state and it can receive pictures over time and then we can be
상태로 근무하고 시간이 지남에 사진을받을 수 있으며, 우리는 할 수 있습니다
some prediction on top of its state in some applications so completely the way
그래서 완전히 일부 응용 프로그램에서 상태의 상단에 몇 가지 예측 방법
this will look like is the Army has some kind of a state which hereunder noting
육군은 지적 이하 상태의 일종을 가지고있는 것처럼이 보일 것이다
as Victor H and this can be also a collection of doctors are just two more
빅터 H하고이 또한 될 수있는 의사의 집합은 두 개있다
general state and we're going to base it as a function of the previous hadn't
일반 상태와 우리는 이전의 함수로의 기반하지 않은거야
state administration time I T minus one and the current input vector 60 and this
하나 뺀 상태 관리 시간 IT 및 현재의 입력 벡터 (60)이
is going to be done through a function which I'll call a recurrence function
내가 재발 함수를 호출합니다 함수를 통해 수행 할 것입니다
and that function will have parameters W and so as we change those W us we're
그 기능은 W 매개 변수가되고 우리는 우리 (W) 그 변경으로 우리는있어
going to see the Arnold different behaviors and then of course we want
물론 우리가 원하는 다음 아놀드 다른 행동을보고 가서
some specific behavior are the Arnon we're going to be training those weights
일부 특정 동작은 아르 논은 우리가 그 무게를 훈련 할 겁니다된다
under seal see examples of that song for now I'd like to note that the same
씰 지금은 그 노래의 예를 참조에서 나는 같은 점에 유의하고 싶습니다
function is used at every single time step with a fixed function of weights w
함수는 무게의 고정 기능 w와 함께 매 시간 단계에서 사용된다
and we played that single function at every single time stuff and that allows
우리는 매번 물건에 그 하나의 기능을 담당하고 허용
us to use the external network on sequences of without having to commit to
우리는 커밋하지 않고 일련의 외부 네트워크를 사용하는
the size of the sequence because we applied the exact same function at every
시퀀스의 크기는 우리의 모든 동일한 기능을 적용하기 때문에
single time step no matter how long the input or output sequences are so in a
한 시간 간격에 상관없이 시간을 입력 또는 출력 순서가 그렇게되어
specific case of recurrent neural network of recurrent neural network the
재발 신경망의 재발 성 신경 네트워크의 특정한 경우
simplest way you can set this up in the simplest recurrence you can use is what
당신이 사용할 수있는 간단한 재발이를 설정할 수 있습니다 간단한 방법은 무엇입니까
other 42 as a bit alarming in this case the state of recurrent neural network is
재발 성 신경 네트워크의 상태가이 경우에 약간의 경고로 (42) 기타
just a single state h and then we have a cross formula that basically tells you
단지 하나의 상태 시간 후 우리는 기본적으로 알려주는 크로스 공식이
how you should update your hidden state age as a function of the previous head
당신은 이전 머리의 함수로 숨겨진 상태 나이를 업데이트하는 방법
of state
국가의
and the current input eckstein and in particular and the simplest case we're
현재 입력 엑스타인 특히 우리가있어 간단한 경우와
going to have these weight matrices whaaa
이러한 가중치 행렬의 whaaa을해야 할 것
WX age and they're going to basically project both in the hidden state from
WX 연령 그들은 기본적으로 숨겨진 상태에서 모두 프로젝트거야
the previous times that in the current input and then those are going to add
다음 현재의 입력과 이들 추가하려고하는 이전의 시간
and then we squish them with at any age and that's how we update the state at
그리고, 우리는 모든 연령에서 그들을 뭉개 버려 그것은 우리가 상태를 업데이트하는 방법
time t so this recurrence is telling you how a total change as a function of its
이 재발 그래서 시간 t는의 함수로 어떻게 전체의 변화를 말하고 그
history and also the current input at this time that and then we can make
역사와 또한이 시간에 현재 입력 한 다음 우리는 할 수 있습니다
predictions we can base predictions on top of H for example using just another
예측은 우리는 또 다른를 사용하여 예를 들어 H의 상단에 예측을 기반으로 할 수 있습니다
matrix projection on top of the hill state so this is the simplest complete
언덕 국가의 상단에 매트릭스 투영 그래서 이것은 단순한 완료
case in which you can wire up in your life work so just give you example of
당신의 인생 작업에 연결할 수있는 경우는, 그래서 그냥 당신의 예를 제공합니다
how this will work right now I'm just talked about sex age and why an abstract
이 지금 작동하는 방법 난 그냥 섹스의 나이와 왜 추상을 이야기 해요
forms in terms of actors we could actually end of these factors with
우리가 실제로 이러한 요인 끝낼 수 배우면에서 형태
semantics and so one of the ways in which we can use a recurrent neural
의미와 방법 그래서 하나는 우리는 재발 성 신경을 사용할 수 있습니다
network as in the case of character level language models and this is one of
문자 레벨 언어 모델의 경우에서와 같이, 네트워크 및이 중 하나이다
my favorite ways of explaining our next because its intuitive and fun to look at
직관적 인과 보는 재미 때문에 우리의 다음 설명의 나의 마음에 드는 방법
so in this case we have character level language models using our dance and the
그래서이 경우에 우리는 우리의 춤과를 사용하여 문자 수준의 언어 모델을
way this will work as we will feed a sequence of characters into the
우리는에 문자의 시퀀스를 공급하므로 방법이 작동
recurring role at work and at every single time step will ask the recurrent
직장과 매 시간 단계에서 역할을 반복하면 재발을 요청합니다
neural network to predict the next character in the sequence will predict
신경망은 시퀀스의 다음 문자를 예측한다 예측할
an entire distribution for what it thinks should come next in the sequence
이 시퀀스에서 다음에 와야 어떻게 생각하는지에 대한 전체 분포
that has seen so far so I suppose that in this very simple example we have the
즉, 지금까지 나는이 아주 간단한 예에서 우리는이 있다고 가정 있도록 보았다
training sequence hello and so we have a vocabulary for characters that are in
트레이닝 시퀀스 안녕하세요 그리고 우리는에있는 문자 어휘가
the ATL and we're going to try to get a recurrent neural network to learn to
ATL의와 우리가 배울 수있는 재발 성 신경 네트워크를 얻으려고하는거야
predict the next character in a sequence on this training data so the way this
이 훈련 데이터에 시퀀스 내의 다음 문자를 예측하는 방법이 너무
will work as will set up will feed in every one of these characters one at a
(A)에서 이러한 문자의 모든 하나 하나에 공급됩니다 설정합니다으로 작동합니다
time into a recurrent neural network you'll see it in a chat the first time
재발 성 신경 네트워크에 시간은 처음 채팅에서 볼 수 있습니다
step and hear the x-axis is the time to time so we'll keep an H II L&L and
단계 및 x 축 듣고 그래서 우리는 H II L & L 및하겠습니다 시간 시간입니다
Hiromi coating characters using what we call it one hot representation where we
히로미 코팅 문자는 우리가 하나의 뜨거운 표현 여기서 우리가 부르는 사용
just turned on the bitter that response to that characters order and vocabulary
그냥 쓴 그 문자에 대응 주문 있고 어휘 켜져
now we're going to use the recurrence formula that I have shown you wear it
지금 우리는 내가 보여 재발 수식 당신이 그것을 착용을 사용하는거야
every single time step suppose we start off with 80 and then we applied this
매 시간 단계는 우리가 80로 시작하고 우리는이 적용된 가정
request to compute the hidden state electorate every single time step using
사용하여 숨겨진 상태 유권자 매 시간 단계를 계산 요청
this fix recurrence formula so I suppose here we have only three percent in state
이 수정 재발의 공식은 그래서 우리는 상태에서 단지 3 %가 여기에 가정
we're going to end up with a three-dimensional representation that
우리는 세 가지 차원 표현으로 끝낼거야 그
basically at any point in time
기본적으로 어느 시점에서
summarizes all the characters that have come until
온까지 모든 문자 요약
and so we have to apply this requires that every single time step and now
그래서 우리는 이것이 필요 적용 할 필요가 매 시간 스텝 지금
we're going to predict that every single time step what should be the next
우리는 매번 다음해야 어떤 단계 것으로 예측거야
character in a sequence so for example since we had four characters in this in
우리는이 네 개의 문자를 가지고 있기 때문에 그래서 예를 들어 시퀀스에서 문자
this we're going to protect the phone numbers at every single time so for
이것은 우리에 대한 그래서 매 시간에 전화 번호를 보호하기 위해거야
example in a very first time that we've said in the letter H and the RNN with
우리는 편지 H와 RNN과에서 말한 아주 처음에 예
its current setting of weights computer these are normalized lock problem he's
무게 컴퓨터의 현재 설정이 그가의 정규화 된 잠금 문제입니다
here for what it thinks should come next
여기 옆에 와서해야한다고 생각하는 것에 대해
so things that H is 110 likely to come next things that eat as 2.2 likely well
H 가능성이 아니라 2.2으로 먹고 다음 일을 올 110 가능성이 있으므로 일
as negative three likely and OS 4.1 likely right now in terms of unless lott
하지 않는 한 로트의 측면에서 가능성이 지금 가능성 및 OS 4.1 세 부정적
probabilities of course we know that in this training sequence we know that we
물론 확률은 우리는이 훈련 순서로 우리가 알고있는 것을 알고 우리가
should follow each so in fact this 2.2 which are shown in green is the correct
녹색으로 표시되어이 2.2가 정확한 사실 때문에 각을 따라야한다
answer in this case and so we want that to be high and we will do all these
이 경우에 답하고 그래서 우리는 그 높은 것으로 원하는 우리는이 모든 작업을 수행합니다
other numbers to be low as on every single time that we have basically a
다른 숫자는 우리가 기본적으로 가지고 매 시간에 낮아야합니다
target for what next character should come in the sequence and so we just want
다음 문자가 순서대로 제공해야하는지에 대한 목표 그래서 우리는 단지 원하는
all these numbers to be high and all the other numbers to be low and so that's of
모든 숫자는 높은하고 다른 모든 숫자는 낮은 것으로 그래서 그의의
course including in the included in the green signal loss function and then that
상기 녹색 신호 손실 함수에 포함하고 있다는 점에서 포함 과정
gets back propagated through these connections so another way to think
다시 이러한 연결 그렇게 생각하는 또 다른 방법을 통해 전파됩니다
about it is that every single time step we basically have a soft max classifier
그것은 매 시간 단계는 우리가 기본적으로 소프트 맥스 분류를 가지고있다에 대해
so every one of these a soft max classifier over the next character and
그래서이 모든 일 다음 문자를 통해 소프트 맥스 분류 및
at every single point we know what the next character should be and so we just
모든 단일 지점에서 우리는 다음 문자가 있어야한다 그래서 우리가 알고
get all those losses slowing down from the top and they will all flow through
모든 손실은 상단에서 아래로 둔화 얻을 그들은 모두를 통과한다
this graph backwards to all the arrows were going to get gradients on all the
모든 화살을 거꾸로이 그래프에서 기울기를 얻기 위하여려고 된 모든
weight matrices and then we'll know how to shift the matrices so that the
체중 행렬 그리고, 우리는 매트릭스를 이동하는 방법을 알게되도록
correct problems are coming out of the Arnon so we'd be shaping those weights
정확한 문제는 우리가 그 무게를 형성 할 것 아르 논에서 나오는된다
so that the correct behavior the army have the correct behaviour you feeding
그 올바른 행동 때문에 군대는 먹이 올바른 동작을
characters as you can imagine how we can turn this over to other questions about
당신과 같은 문자는 우리에 대한 다른 질문이 뒤집 수있는 방법을 상상할 수있다
the diagram
그림
yeah Thank you so desperately lying as I mentioned a scene the recurrence the
그래 나는 장면을 되풀이을 언급 한 바와 같이 그렇게 필사적으로 거짓말을 주셔서 감사합니다
same functions always so we have a single WX patient every time step we
항상 동일한 기능 그래서 우리는 하나의 WX 환자마다 단계 우리가
have a single WHYY at every time step in the same whah applied at every time step
같은 whah의 모든 시간 단계에서 하나의 WHYY마다 단계에 적용했습니다
here so we've used WX awh why awhh four times in this diagram and in back
여기에서 우리는 WX를 사용했습니다 AWH 이유도 및 다시 awhh 네 번
propagation when we get through YouTube account for that because we'll have all
우리 모두를해야하기 때문에 전파 우리는 YouTube에 계정을 통해 얻을 때
these gradients adding up to the same weight matrix because it has been used
동일한 가중치 행렬을 더하여 이들 구배는 사용 되었기 때문에
at multiple time steps and this is what allows us to process you know variably
여러 시간 단계와에 이것은 당신이 가변적으로 알고 처리 할 수​​있게 해준다 것입니다
sized inputs because every time that we're doing the same thing so not a
크기 입력 우리는 같은 일을 그렇게하지 ​​않는 일을하는지마다 때문에
function of the absolute amount of things and your question what are common
사물의 절대 금액의 기능과 공통 무엇인지 질문
things for initializing the first 80 I think US Senate 20 this quite quite
제 80 초기화하는 일이 내가 생각하는 미국 상원 (20)이 아주 아주
common in the beginning but does the order in which will receive the data
처음에 공통되지만 순서에 따라 데이터를 수신처 않는다
that matter
그 문제
yes because so are you asking for these characters in a different order so if
예 있기 때문에 그래서 당신은 만약 그렇다면 다른 순서로 이러한 문자를 요구하고
you see if this was a longer sequence the order in this case in this case
이이 경우에는이 경우의 순서 긴 시퀀스 않았는지
always doesn't matter because it every single point in time if you think about
당신에 대해 생각하면 항상 시간에하기 때문에 하나 하나 점을 중요하지 않습니다
it functionally like this it's a factor at this time step as a function of
그것은 기능적 같이 이것은 팩터의 함수로서 시간이 단계에서의
everything that has come before it right and so disorder just matters for as long
그것은 바로 그래서 장애는 그냥 오랫동안 중요한 전에 온 모든
as you're reading it and we're going to go through a sieve through some specific
당신이 그것을 읽고있는 것처럼 우리는 몇 가지 구체적인 통해 체를 통해 갈거야
examples which i think will clarify some of these points to look at a specific
나는 이러한 점들을 명확히 생각 예는 특정보고하기
example in fact if you want to try to characterize the language model it's
당신은 그것의 언어 모델의 특성을 시도 할 경우 실제로 예
quite short so I wrote a just then you can find a good home where this is
이 곳에 아주 짧은 그래서 난 그냥 당신이 좋은 가정을 찾을 수를 썼다
hundred line application in numpy for accuracy level are and then you can go
정확도 수준 NumPy와 백에 줄 응용 프로그램입니다 그리고 당신은 갈 수 있습니다
through an actual active steps through this with you so you can see concretely
당신이를 통해 실제 활성 단계 그래서 당신은 구체적으로 볼 수 있습니다
how we could train a recurrent neural network impact this and so I'm going to
우리는이 재발 신경 네트워크에 미치는 영향을 훈련 할 수 그래서 내가 갈거야 방법
step through this so we're going to go through all the blocks in the beginning
이 때문에 우리는 처음에 모든 블록을 통해 갈거야 단계별로
as you'll see the only dependence here is we're loading in some text data so
당신은 여기에만 의존은 우리가 일부 텍스트 데이터를로드하는 것을 볼 수 있습니다로
our input here is just a large collection of a large sequence of
여기에 우리의 입력의 큰 순서 그냥 큰 모음입니다
characters in this case a text input that txt file and then we get all the
이 경우 문자 파일을 TXT하고 우리 모두가 얻을 텍스트 입력
characters in that file and we find all the unique characters in that file
해당 파일의 문자 우리는 해당 파일의 모든 고유 문자를 찾을 수
create these mapping dictionaries that map from characteristic in the season
계절의 특성에 매핑이 매핑 사전을 만들
from indices two characters we basically order our characters so seeming bread in
인덱스에서 두 문자 우리는 기본적으로 우리의 문자가 너무 빵을 보이는 주문
a whole bunch of to file and a whole bunch of data and we have hundred
파일로의 전체 무리와 데이터의 전체 무리 우리 백 한
characters or something like that and ordered them in a in a sequence so we
문자 나처럼 뭔가 그래서 우리는 순서에 그들을 주문
associate indices to every character men here we're going to diminish license
여기에 모든 문자 남자에 연관 지수는 우리는 라이센스를 감소거야
first are hidden sizes hyper primary as you'll see with recurrent neural
당신이 재발 성 신경로 볼 수 있습니다로 첫 번째 하이퍼 기본 크기 숨겨져 있습니다
networks so you aren't using it to be a hundred here we have a learning rate
그렇게하면 네트워크 우리는 학습율이 여기 백으로 사용하지 않을
sequence length here is up to twenty-five this is a parameter that
스물 다섯이이 매개 변수가 최대 여기 시퀀스 길이입니다
you'll be you'll become aware of what the problem is if our input data is way
우리의 입력 데이터가 길 경우 당신은 문제가 무엇인지 알게 될 것입니다 수 있습니다
too large say like millions of times the UPS there's no way you can put in
시간의 수백만 같은 너무 큰 말은 UPS는 당신이 넣을 수있는 방법은 없습니다
dhahran and on top of all of it because we need to maintain all of the stuff and
다란과의 모든 위에 우리가 물건을 모두 유지할 필요가 있기 때문에
memory so that you can do back propagation in fact we won't be able to
당신이 실제로 전파를 다시 할 수 있도록 메모리 우리는 할 수 없습니다
keep all of it and two men in memory and a back rub through all of it so we'll go
우리가 갈거야 그것 모두를 통해 그것의 모든 메모리와 다시 문질러 두 남자를 유지
in chunks through our input data in this case we're going through chunks of 25 at
이 경우 우리의 입력 데이터를 통해 덩어리로 우리는 25의 덩어리에서 통해거야
a time so as you'll see in a bit
당신은 약간의 시간을 볼 수 있도록
we have this entire dataset but will be going in chunks of 25 characters at a
우리는이 전체 데이터 집합을 가지고 있지만 25 문자의 덩어리로 갈 것
time and every time we're just going to backup get through 25 characters on time
시간과 우리가 백업거야 때마다 시간에 25 자 통과
because we can't afford to do back propagation for longer because we have
우리는 우리가 가지고 있기 때문에 이상에 대한 전파을 다시 할 여유가 없기 때문에
to remember all that stuff and so we're going in chunks here of 25 and then we
모든 물건을 기억하고 우리는 여기에 25 그리고 우리 덩어리거야
have all these W matrices that here I'm analyzing randomly and some boxes so WX
모두 여기에 내가 무작위로 분석하고있어 이러한 W 행렬과 일부 상자 WX 그래서이
HHH and HY and those are all of our hype all of our parameters that we're going
HHH와 HY 그 우리의 매개 변수의 모든 과대 광고의 모든 우리는 거 야된다
to train a backrub
backrub를 양성하는
I'm going to skip over the loss function here and I'm going to get to the bottom
나는 여기에 손실 함수를 통해 건너 갈거야 내가 바닥에 도착하는거야
of the script here we have a main loop and I'm going to go through some of this
여기에 스크립트의 우리는 메인 루프를 가지고 있고이 중 일부를 통해 갈거야
may look now so there are some initialization here of various things 20
여기에 다양한 몇 가지 초기화가 그래서 20 지금 보일 수 있습니다
in the beginning and then we're looking for ever
다음 처음에 우리는 영원히 찾고
we're doing here is a sampling a batch of data so here it is where I actually
우리가 여기서하고있는 것은 그래서 여기에 데이터의 배치가 어디 실제로 샘플링
take a batch of 25 characters out of this dataset so that's in the list
그 목록에, 그래서이 데이터 세트에서 25 문자의 배치를 취할
inputs and the list and puts basically just has 25 integers correspond to the
입력하고 목록 및 둔다는 기본적으로 단지가 25 정수는 대응
characters the targets as you'll see is just all the same characters but offset
당신이 볼로 문자 대상은 모두 같은 문자하지만 오프셋
by one because those are the indices that we're trying to predict it every
하나 그 때문에 우리는 모든을 예측하려는 인덱스는
single time stuff so so important targets are just list of 25 characters
한 시간에 물건을 너무 중요한 목표는 25 자에 불과 목록입니다
targets as offset by one into the future so that's what we sampled basically back
즉 우리가 기본적으로 샘플링 무엇 때문에 대상은 같은 미래에 의해 오프셋 (offset)
from data here we this is some sample code so it every single point in time
여기에 데이터에서 우리이는 그래서 몇 가지 예제 코드는 시간의 모든 단일 지점
training this week and of course I try to generate some samples of what it's
이번 주 훈련 물론 내가하려고하는 것은 그것이 무엇의 일부 샘플을 생성하는
currently thanks character should actually what these sequences look like
현재 감사 문자는 이러한 순서는 다음과 같이 보일 것입니다 실제로 무엇을
the way we use character low-level artists and test time is that we're
우리는 문자 낮은 수준의 예술가와 테스트 시간을 사용하는 방법은 우리가 걸이다
going to see that with some characters and then this aren't always gives us the
다음 몇 가지 문자와 함께이 항상 아니라는 것을 보게 될 것은 우리에게주는
distribution of the next character in a sequence so you can imagine sampling
당신이 샘플링을 상상할 수 있도록 시퀀스에서 다음 문자의 분포
from it and then you feat in the next character getting a sample from the
그것에서 다음 다음 문자의 위업은에서 샘플을 받고
distribution and keep doing it in to keep feeding all the samples into the
분포와에 모든 샘플을 공급 유지에 그 일을 계속
iron and you can just generate arbitrary text data that's what this code will do
철, 당신은이 코드가 무엇을 할 것입니다 그 임의의 텍스트 데이터를 생성 할 수 있습니다
and it caused the sample function so we're going to that in a bit then here
그리고 우리가 여기에 약간의 그 거 야 그래서 샘플 기능을 발생
I'm calling the loss function the loss function receives the inputs the targets
I는 손실 함수는 입력 대상을받는 손실 함수를 호출있어
and it receives also this H prep H pressure is short for his state vector
그리고이 H 준비 H 압력이 자신의 상태 벡터에 대한 짧은 또한 수신
from the previous trunk so we're going in batches of 25 and we are keeping
이전 트렁크에서 우리는 (25)의 일괄거야 그리고 우리는 유지됩니다
track of what is the latest a picture at the end of your 25 letters so that we
당신의 25 편지의 끝 부분에있는 최신 사진이 무엇인지를 추적하는 우리
can when we meet in the next back we can see that in as the initial h at that
우리가 다음에 다시 만날 때 우리는 그의 초기 시간으로 그에서 볼 수 있습니다
time so we're making sure that the hidden states are basically correctly
우리가 숨겨진 상태가 제대로 기본적으로있는 것을 확인하고, 그래서 시간
propagated from batch to batch through that but we're only back propagating
그 통해 일괄 배치에서 전파 그러나 우리는 다시 전파하는
those 25 time steps so we fit into a function of the loss and gradients and
그 25 시간 단계 그래서 우리는 손실 및 그라디언트의 기능에 적합하고
all the weight matrices and all the boxes and you're just printing the loss
모든 무게 행렬과 모든 상자와 당신은 손실을 인쇄하고
and then here's a primer update we're told us older greetings and here we are
그리고 여기에 우리가 여기에 우리가 우리에게 나이 인사를 듣는다 프라이머 업데이트 그리고
actually perform the update which you should recognize as an undergrad update
실제로 당신이 대학원에 업데이트로 인식해야 업데이트를 수행
so I have all these cash to think of all these cashed
그래서 나는이 현금으로 모든 생각하는 모든 현금이
variables for the gradient squared which I'm accumulating and then perform the
그라데이션에 대한 변수는 내가 축적 한 다음를 수행하고있어 어느 제곱
autocratic date someone to go into the loss function and what that looks like
독재 날짜 누군가가 손실 함수로 이동하고 어떻게 그처럼 보인다
now the loss function is this block of code it really consists of forward and
이제 손실 함수는 정말 앞으로 구성 코드 블록이며,
backward method so we're comparing the forward pass and then the back of
우리가 앞으로 패스 다음의 뒷면을 비교하는, 그래서 뒤로 방법
passing Green so I'll go through those two steps forward pass you should
녹색 그래서이 두 단계를 통해 갈거야 통과하면 앞으로해야 당신에게 전달
recognize basically we get those deficit targets we're waiting receive these 25
기본적으로 우리는 우리가 기다리고있어 그 적자 대상이 25를받을 얻을 인식
indices and we're not trading through them from 1 to 25 we create this text
인덱스 우리는 25 일에서 그들을 통해 거래하지 않는 우리는이 텍스트를 만들
input vector which is just zeros and then we set the one hot encoding so
그럼 그냥 제로이며, 입력 벡터 우리는 그래서 하나의 뜨거운 인코딩을 설정
whatever the index and impetus we turned it on for with one so we're feeding in
어떤 인덱스 및 자극 우리는 하나 우리가에 공급하고 그것을 설정
the character with that one hot encoding
그 하나의 뜨거운 인코딩 문자
here in computing the recurrence formula using this equation so hsi T
여기에이 식 HSI T 그래서를 사용하여 재발 수식을 계산에
their ages and all these things to keep track of everything and every single
자신의 연령이 모든 것을 다하고 하나 하나 추적하기
time stuff so we compute the state vector and the output using the
시간 물건 그래서 우리는 상태 벡터와를 사용하여 출력을 계산
recurrence formula and these two lines and then over there I'm computing the
재발 수식이 두 줄 다음 저기 난을 계산 해요
suspects function so normalizing this so that if we get probabilities and then
그래서 용의자 그래서이 정상화 작동하는지 우리는 확률을 얻을 경우
your loss is negative lock probability of the correct answer so that's just a
그 그냥 그래서 당신의 손실은 정답의 부정적인 잠금 확률
softness classifier lost over there so that's the purpose and we're going to
부드러움의 분류는 그 목적 그래서 거기 잃고 우리는 거 야
back propagate through the graph so in the backward pass we go backwards
우리가 뒤로 이동 뒤로 패스 그래서 다시 그래프를 통해 전파
through that sequence from 25
(25)로부터의 순서를 통해
all the way back to one and maybe you'll recognize I don't know how much detail I
당신은 내가 인식합니다 다시 하나 어쩌면 모든 방법은 얼마나 많은 세부 사항을 모르는 I
want to go in here but you'll recognize them back propagating through a soft max
여기에 가고 싶어하지만 당신은 소프트 맥스를 통해 전파를 다시 인식합니다
propagating through the activation functions I'm not propagating through
내가 통해 전파하고 있지 않다 활성화 기능을 통해 전파
all of it and I'm just adding up all the greetings and all the prime minister and
그것의 모든 난 그냥 모든 인사 및 모든 총리을 추가 해요
one thing to note here especially is that these ingredients and make weight
특히 여기에서주의해야 할 한 가지는 이러한 재료와 무게를 만드는 것입니다
matrices like woahh I'm using a plus equals because it every single time step
내가 플러스를 사용하고 woahh 같은 행렬에 해당 그것은 매 시간 스텝 때문에
all of these weight matrices getting gradient and we need to accumulate
이 무게의 모든 그라데이션을 받고 행렬 우리는 축적해야
fit into all the weight matrices because we keep using all these weight matrices
우리는 이러한 모든 체중 행렬을 계속 사용하기 때문에 모든 체중 행렬에 적합
at the same at every time step and so we just backdrop into them over time and
시간이 지남에 그들로 때마다 단계에서 동일한 그래서 우리 그냥 배경에서와
that gives us the radiance and then we can use that loss function from the
그것은 우리에게 생기를 제공하고 우리는에서 그 손실 기능을 사용할 수 있습니다
primary and then here we have finally a sampling function so here is where we
기본 및 여기에 우리는 마침내 그래서 여기에 샘플링 기능은 어디 한 우리
try to actually get the artist to generate new text data based on what he
실제로 그 내용에 기초하여 새로운 텍스트 데이터를 생성하는 아티스트 가려고
has seen an attorney and based on the statistics of the characters and how
캐릭터와 방법의 통계에 변호사를 보았고를 기반으로하고있다
they follow each other in the training data so we initialize with some rain and
우리는 약간의 비와 함께 초기화 그래서 그들은 훈련 데이터에서 서로를 따라
character and then we go for until we get tired and we compute the recurrence
문자, 그리고, 우리는 우리가 피곤 때까지 가서 우리가 재발을 계산
formula that the problem the distribution sample from the
식 문제로부터 배포 샘플이
distribution
분포
encoded in one hot Kate 11 hot representation and then we fielded a
핫 케이트 (11) 핫 표현으로 인코딩 한 후 우리는을 받​​았는데
next time so we keep doing this until we actually get 200 texts so is there any
우리가 실제로 200 텍스트를 얻을 때까지 우리가이 일을 계속 그래서 다음에 시간이 너무 거기 어떤
question over just like the rough layout of how this works
그냥이 작동하는 방법의 거친 레이아웃 등을 통해 질문
$25 South max classifiers at every batch and we back all of those at the same
다시 $ (25) 남부 최대의 모든 배치에서 분류 우리 같은에서 사람들의 모든
time and all add up in the connections going backwards that's why do we use
시간과 모든 우리가 사용하는 왜 거꾸로 그건가는 연결에 추가
regularization here you'll see that I probably do not I guess I skipped it
여기 정규화 당신은 내가 그것을 생략 추측 아마하지 않는 것을 확인할 수 있습니다
here but you can in general I think sometimes I tried regularization I don't
때때로 나는 정규화를 시도 여기에 있지만 일반적으로 내가 생각할 수있는 난 몰라
think it is common to use it and recurring nuts as outside sometimes it
때로는 그것을 외부로 반복 너트를 사용하는 것이 일반적이다 생각
gave me like worst results so sometimes I skip it it's kind of a fight promoter
최악의 결과처럼 내게 준 것은 그래서 가끔 그것을 싸움 발기인의 그것의 종류를 건너
yeah that's right yeah that's right so in the sequence of 25 shots here we are
그래 그건 그래 그건 우리가 바로 여기에 25 샷의 순서 그래서 바로
very low level on character level and we don't actually care about words we don't
매우 낮은 캐릭터 레벨에 대한 수준과 우리가 실제로 단어에 대해 걱정하지 않는다 우리는하지 않습니다
know that word exists as just character indices so miss arnelle in fact doesn't
그 단어는 사실은 그렇지 않습니다에서처럼 문자 인덱스가 너무 arnelle를 그리워 존재 알고
know anything about characters so language or anything like that just in
같은 언어 또는 아무것도 그냥 그렇게 문자에 대해 아는
the series and sequences appendices and that's what we're modeling using pieces
시리즈와 시퀀스 부록에 그 우리가 사용하는 조각을 모델링하고 무엇
can be used space as the letters or something like that instead of just
대신 그 같은 문자로 공간 또는 뭔가를 사용할 수 있습니다
constant batches of 25 I think he maybe could but then it kind of just you have
25 일정 배치는 그가 아마 할 수 생각하지만 다음 종류의 단지, 당신은
to make assumptions about language will see soon why you would want to do that
당신이 그렇게 할 이유 언어에 대한 가정이 곧 볼 수 있도록합니다
because you can plug anything into this and we'll see that we can have a lot of
이에 아무것도 연결할 수 있습니다 그리고 우리는 우리가 많이 가질 수 있음을 볼 수 있기 때문에
fun with that ok now we can do we can take a whole bunch of texts we don't
그 확인과 재미 이제 우리는 우리가 텍스트의 전체 무리를 우리가하지 걸릴 수 있습니다 할 수있는
care where it came from a sequence of characters and we feed into the Arnon
이 문자의 순서 어디에서 왔는지 신경 그리고 우리는 아르 논에 공급
and we can train the iron and to create text like it and so for example you can
우리는 철을 훈련 할 수 있으며 같은 텍스트를 작성하고 그래서 예를 들어, 당신은 할 수 있습니다
take all of William Shakespeare's works you can catch all of it is just a giant
당신이 그것을 모두 잡을 수 있습니다 윌리엄 셰익스피어의 작품을 모두 가지고 그냥 거대한입니다
sequence of characters and you put into the recurrent neural network and try to
문자의 순서 당신은 재발 성 신경 네트워크에 넣고 시도
predict the next character in a sequence for William Shakespeare proponents and
윌리엄 셰익스피어의 지지자에 대한 시퀀스에서 다음 문자를 예측하고
so when you do those of course in the beginning the recurrent neural network
그래서 당신은 처음에 재발 신경망을 물론 그 작업을 수행 할 때
has random random parameters so just producing a garbled at the very end so
그래서 그냥 바로 종료 그래서에서 왜곡을 생산 무작위 임의의 매개 변수가
it's just random characters but then when you train the Arnon will start to
그냥 임의의 문자를이다 그러나 당신이 훈련 할 때 다음 아르 논가에 시작됩니다
understand that ok there are actually things like spaces there's words start
그 확인을 이해 거기의 말을 시작 공백이 같은 일이 실제로있다
to experiment with quotes it and it basically learn some of the very short
따옴표와 함께 실험은 그것은 기본적으로 매우 짧은 일부 내용
words like here or on and so on and then as you train more and more disease
당신이 더 많은 질병 훈련으로 여기거나 등등 다음과 같은 단어
becomes more and more refined and the recurrent neural network learns that
되고 점점 더 세련되고 재발 신경 네트워크를 배운다
when you open a quote you should close it later or that those sentences and
당신이 견적을 열 때 나중에 닫거나해야하는 그 문장
with a cup with a dot it learns all the stuff statistically just from the rock
점과 한잔과 함께 그냥 바위에서 통계적으로 모든 물건을 배운다
patterns without actually having to head coach anything and in the end you can
실제로 코치 아무것도 머리를하지 않고 당신이 할 수있는 말의 패턴
sample entire
샘플 전체
shakespeare based on this on a character level so just give an idea about what
캐릭터 레벨이 기반으로 셰익스피어 그래서 그냥에 대한 아이디어를 줄 것
kind of stuff comes out a lot I think he shall become approached and the gang
물건의 종류 나는 그가 접근 될 것이다 생각을 많이하고 갱을 제공
will strain would be attained into being never fed and his but the chain and
존재에 달성 될 것이다 변형됩니다 공급하지 않고 자신 만 체인 결코
subject of his death I should not sleep
내가 잠을 안 그의 죽음의 주제
that's the kind of stuff that you would get out of this regard network you're
즉, 당신이있어 이와 관련하여 네트워크의 나갈 것입니다 물건의 종류
mean up a very subtle point which I'd like to get back to you in a bit okay so
내가 좋아 그래서 비트에 다시 연락하고 싶은 아주 미묘한 점을 의미
we can run this on Shakespeare but we can run the Sun basically anything so
우리는 셰익스피어에서이 작업을 실행할 수 있지만 우리는 그래서 기본적으로 아무것도 태양을 실행할 수 있습니다
we're playing with this with Justin I think like roughly year ago and so
우리는 내가 대략 년 전 등처럼 생각 저스틴과 함께이 함께 연주
Justin Tuck he found this book on algebraic geometry and this is just a
저스틴 턱 그는 대수 기하학에서이 책을 발견하고이 단지입니다
large latex source file and we took that latex source file for this geometry and
대형 라텍스 소스 파일 우리는이 형상에 대해 그 라텍스 소스 파일을 가져다
finance the art and the artist can learn to basically generate mathematics so
예술을 재정 작가는 기본적으로 수학을 그렇게 생성을 배울 수
this is a sample submitted this morning just spits out late check and then we
이 아침에 제출 된 샘플 그냥 다음 늦은 체크 아웃 뱉어이며 우리
can pilot and of course doesn't work right away we had to tune it a tiny bit
파일럿 물론 바로 작동하지 않습니다으로 우리는 조정 그것은 작은 비트를 가지고 있습니다
but basically the Arnon after we tweaked some of the mistakes that has made you
하지만 기본적으로 아르 논은 우리가 당신을 만든 실수의 일부를 불통 후
can compile it and you can get the generate mathematics as you'll see that
컴파일 할 수 있습니다 당신은 당신이 그것을 볼로 수학을 생성 얻을 수 있습니다
it basically creates all these proofs it puts her stupid little squares at the
그것은 기본적으로는 그녀의 바보 같은 작은 사각형을두고 이러한 모든 증거를 생성
end of troops it creates let us and so on
군대의 끝은 그렇게에 우리를 보자 생성
sometimes we are going to create diagrams to varying amounts of success
때때로 우리는 성공의 다양한 양으로 다이어그램을 만들 예정
and my best my favorite part about this is that on the top left the proof here
그리고 이것에 대해 최선 나의 마음에 드는 부분은 상단에 여기 증거가 남아 있다는 것입니다
is emitted
방출된다
the Sarno is just lazy but otherwise this stuff is quite indistinguishable I
Sarno는 게으른하지만 그렇지 않으면이 물건은 확실히 구별 I입니다
would say from from actual geometry so let X 10 scheme of X ok I'm not sure
실제 형상에서에서 말을 그래서 X의 X 10 방식을하자 확인 나는 확실하지 않다
about that part but otherwise the gestalt of this looks very good
그 부분에 대한하지만 그렇지 않으면이의 게슈탈트 매우 좋아 보인다
arbitrary things that it so I tried to find the hardest arbitrary thing that I
그것이 내가 가장 어려운 임의의 일을 찾기 위해 노력 임의의 물건이 I
could throw the character level I decided that source code is actually
캐릭터 레벨을 던질 수 있었다 나는 소스 코드를 실제로 결정
very difficult so I took all of Linux source which is just older like C code
매우 어려운 그래서 C 코드와 같은 단지 이전 인 리눅스 소스의 모든했다
you can copy it and you end up with I think some hundred megabytes and just
당신은 그것을 복사 할 수 있습니다 당신은 내가 몇 백 메가 바이트 생각으로 끝낼 단지
see code and header files and then just thrown into the Arnon and then it can
코드와 헤더 파일을 참조하고 단지 아르 논에 던져 그리고, 그것은 할 수
learn to generate code and so this is generated code from the Arnon and you
아르 논 당신의 코드 등이 생성 된 코드를 생성하는 법을 배워야
can see that basically creates function declarations it knows about inputs
그것을 볼 수 있습니다 기본적으로는 입력에 대해 알고 함수 선언을 만듭니다
syntactically it makes very few mistakes it knows about variables sort of how to
구문 그것은 일종의 변수에 대해 알고 거의 실수를하는 방법을
use them sometimes it intends to code it creates its own bogus comments
그들이 때때로 그것을 코딩 할 계획 사용은 자신의 가짜 코멘트를 작성
syntactically is very rare to find that it would open a bracket and not close it
구문은 브라켓을 열고 닫습니다하지 않을 것을 발견하는 것은 매우 드문 일이다
and so on this actually is relatively easy for dornin to learn and so some of
dornin 그래서 몇 가지를 배우고하는 등이에 실제로 상대적으로 쉽다
the mistakes that makes actually is that for example it
실제로 만드는 실수는 그 예를 들어 그
declare some variables that it never ends up using or do the same variables
그것을 사용하여 결코 끝나지 않아 몇 가지 변수를 선언하거나 동일한 변수를 할
that it never declared and so some of these high level stuff is still missing
이 선언되지 않습니다 그래서 이러한 높은 수준의 물건 중 일부는 아직 행방 불명된다
but otherwise it can do just fine
하지만 그렇지 않으면 잘 할 수있는
it also no hostile recite the Jeep the new GOP licensed character by character
그것은 또한 더 적대적는 지프 새로운 GOP에게 문자로 허가 된 문자를 암송하지
that has learned from data and that knows that after the GPL license there
그는 데이터에서 배운하고는 GPL 라이센스 후이 알고있다
some include files there some macros and then there's some code so that's
일부는이 파일의 일부 매크로를 포함하고는, 그래서 다음 몇 가지 코드가있다
basically what has learned that in turn into just a show is very small
기본적으로 그냥 쇼에 교대로 매우 작은 것이 무엇인지를 배웠다
just a toy thing to show you what's going on then there's a char and then
그냥 장난감 일이 일어나고 다음 문자 거기하고 있는지를 보여
which is a more kind of implementation and torch which has just been charged
그냥 충전 된 구현 및 토치의 많은 종류는이다
and scaled up and runs and GPU and so you can play with that yourself and so
과 및 실행과 GPU를 확장 그래서 당신은 자신을 재생할 수 등
this in particular was going to this by then the latter it's a three-layer Alice
이 특히 그것이 세 계층 앨리스의 다음 후자에 의해이 가고 있었다
team and so we'll see what that means it's a more complex kind of phone
팀 그리고 우리는 그게 전화의 더 복잡한 종류의 의미를 볼 수 있습니다
network I just give an idea about how this works so there's a paper that we
난 그냥이 어떻게 작동하는지에 대한 아이디어를 제공 네트워크는 그래​​서 종이가 있음을 우리
played with a lot but this was just an last year and we're basically trying to
많은 연주 그러나 이것은 단지 작년 우리는 기본적으로 노력하고
pretend that we're neuroscientists and we threw a hair salon on some test text
우리는 신경 과학자있어 척 그리고 우리는 몇 가지 테스트 텍스트에 미용실을 던졌다
and so the Arden is reading this text in the snippet of code and we're looking at
그래서 아덴의 코드 스 니펫에서이 텍스트를 읽고 우리가보고있는
a specific cell and his state of the art coloring the text based on whether or
특정 셀의 여부에 기초하여 상기 텍스트 착색 당해 그의 상태
not that sells excited or not
하지 그 흥분 판매 여부
ok so you can see that many of the state
확인 그래서 당신은 국가의 많은 볼 수 있습니다
neurons are not interpretable to kind of fire on nothin kind of weird ways
뉴런은 이상한 방법으로 아무것도의 종류에 화재의 종류에 해석되지 않습니다
because they have to do some of them have to do quite low level character
그들이해야하기 때문에 그들 중 일부는 매우 낮은 수준의 문자를해야
level stuff like how often does she come after age and stuff like that let's all
그녀는하자 모두 같은 나이와 물건 후에 오는가 얼마나 자주 같은 수준의 물건
the cells are quite interpretable so for example we find ourselves like a quick
우리는 빠른처럼 자신을 찾을 예를 들면 있도록 세포는 아주 해석입니다
detection so that this cell just turns on when it is a quote and then it stays
검출 있도록이 셀은 그냥 인용 한 때 온 후는 유지
on until the quote closets and so this quite reliably keeps track of this and
인용 옷장까지에 등이 매우 안정적이 추적을 유지하고
it just comes out from backpropagation the island of this size that the
그냥 역 전파에서이 크기의 섬을 나오는 그
character level statistics are different inside and outside of course and this is
캐릭터 레벨 통계 물론 내외 다르며이다
a useful feature to learn and so it dedicate some of its head of state to
유용한 기능은 학습하고 그래서 그것의 머리 상태의 일부를 바칩니다
keeping track of whether or not you're inside a quote and this goes back to
당신이 따옴표 안에있어 여부를 추적하고이로 돌아갑니다
your question which I want to point out here that this RNN was trained on I
나는이 RNN가 I에 훈련 것을 여기에서 지적하고 싶은 질문
think sequence length
시퀀스 길이를 생각한다
hundred but if you measure the length of this quote is actually much more than a
백하지만 당신은이 인용문의 길이가 실제로보다 훨씬 더 측정 할 경우
hundred i think is like 250 and so we worked on we only back propagated up to
내가 생각 백 (250)처럼 우리는 다시 최대 전파에 그래서 우리는 일
a hundred and so that's the only place where the cell can actually like Lauren
백은 그래서는 셀 수 실제로 로렌 같은 유일한 장소
itself because it wouldn't be able to spot the appendices there much longer
자체는 더 이상이 부록을 발견 할 수 없습니다 때문에
than that but I think basically this seems to show that you can train this
그러나보다 기본적으로 내가이이 훈련을 수 있다는 것을 보여 것 같아요
character level detection sell as a useful on sequences less than a hundred
캐릭터 레벨 검출 백보다 작은 시퀀스에 유용한로 판매
and then it generalizes properly to longer sequences so this so this cell
다음은이 때문에이 셀 수 있도록 긴 시퀀스에 제대로 일반화
seems to work for more than a hundred steps even if it was only trained even
그것은 단지에도 교육을받은 경우 더 이상 백 단계를 작동하는 것 같다
if it was only able to spot the dependencies on less than a hundred this
그것보다 수백이의 종속성을 발견 할 만 할 수 있다면
is another dataset here this is I think Leo Tolstoy's War and Peace this is in
이 여기에 다른 데이터 세트 내가 레오 톨스토이의 전쟁과 평화는이에 생각이다
this dataset there's a new line character at every single at roughly 80
이 데이터 세트는 대략 80 매에서 새 줄 문자있다
characters in 80 characters roughly there's a new line and there's a there's
80 자 문자 대략 새로운 라인이있다 그리고 거기에있다
a line link tracking so that we found where it starts off at like one and then
그 다음 하나 같은에서 시작은 우리가 찾을 수 있도록 라인 링크 추적
it slowly case over time and you might imagine that a cell like this is
천천히 시간이 지남에 따라 구분하고이 같은 세포가 있음을 상상
actually very useful in predicting that you like character at the end because
당신이 말 때문에에 캐릭터를 좋아하는 예측 실제로 매우 유용
this arnie's to count a tee time steps so that it knows when a new line
이 때 새로운 라인을 알 수 있도록이 애니의 티 타임 단계를 계산하는
character is likely to come next
문자는 다음에 올 가능성이 높습니다
ok so there's like tracking tell us we found cells that actually respond only a
확인 그래서 추적처럼 거기에 우리가 실제로 단지 응답 세포를 발견 알려
sudden statements we found cells that only respondents cite quotes and strings
갑자기 문을 우리는 응답자가 시세 및 문자열을 인용 세포 발견
we found cells that I get more excited the deeper you nestin expression and so
우리는 내가 깊은 당신이 네 스틴 표현 등을 더 흥분 세포 발견
all kinds of interesting cells that you can actually find inside these are not
실제로이 내부에서 찾을 수 있습니다 흥미로운 세포의 모든 종류는 아니다
completely come out just from the back propagation and so that's quite magical
완전하게 다시 전파에서 나와서 그래서 아주 마법의
I suppose but
나는 생각하지만,
this Alice team I think they're about 2,100 cell so you just gonna go through
당신은 그냥 통과거야 그래서 내가 생각하는이 앨리스 팀은 약 2,100 세포있어
them and some of them look like this but I would say roughly 5 percent of them
그들과 그들 중 일부는 다음과 같이하지만 그 중 약 5 %를 말할 것입니다
you spot something interesting so you just go through it manually
그냥 수동으로 통과, 그래서 당신은 뭔가 흥미로운 것을 발견
sorry so we are completely running the entire are in an intact but we're only
미안 우리가 완전히 전체를 실행하는 온전한에 있지만 우리는있어
looking at a single hidden state fire at the firing of US one single cell in
US 하나의 셀의 소성시 하나의 숨겨진 상태 화재를보고
dhahran so running the are normally but we're just kind of a recording from one
다란 그래서 일반적으로하지만 우리는 하나에서 기록의 단지 친절 실행
cell and the hidden state that makes sense so this sell just the entire are
전지 등이 단지 전체가 판매하는 의미가 숨겨진 상태
among those rising one part of the hidden state basically there's many
숨겨진 상태의 그 상승 한 부분 사이에 기본적으로 많은있다
other hidden still hittin cells that involved in different ways and they're
다른 하나는 여전히 다른 방법에 관련된 세포를 잤지 숨겨진 그들이있어
all believing in different times and they're all doing different things
모든 다른 시간에 믿고 그들은 모두 다른 일을하고있는
inside the Arnon hidden state
아르 논 숨겨진 상태 내부
but you can get similar results with one layer
하지만 당신은 하나의 층으로 비슷한 결과를 얻을 수 있습니다
these cells were always between negative one in 110 each and this is from
이 세포는 (110) 각각에 부정적 일 사이에 항상 있었고,이은이다
analysis team which we haven't covered yet but the firing of the salsa between
우리가 아직 덮여 있지만, 살사의 소성 사이하지 않은 분석 팀
a one and one so that's the scale that's us this picture so are as are pretty
하나 하나는 그래서 꽤 있습니다 정도로되어 우리에게이 사진의 규모이다
cool and you can actually trendy sequence models over time about roughly
시원하고 트렌디 한 시퀀스 모델 시간이 지남에 실제로 수에 대한 대략
one year ago several people have come to realize that you can actually use the
일년 전 여러 사람이 실제로 사용할 수 있음을 깨닫게했다
same very neat application in the context of computer vision to perform
수행 할 수있는 컴퓨터 비전의 맥락에서 같은 매우 깔끔한 응용 프로그램
image capturing in this context for taking a single imagine we'd like to
하나의 복용이 상황에서 캡처 이미지는 우리가하고 싶은 상상
describe it with a sequence of warrants and these are nuns are very good at
보증의 순서로 설명하고이 있습니다 수녀은 아주 좋다
understanding how sequences develop over time so in this particular model them
이 특정 모델 그들 있도록 시퀀스는 시간이 지남에 따라 개발 방법을 이해
going to describe this actually work from roughly year-ago happens to be my
이 실제로 대략에서 일을 설명하려고 전년 될 일이 내
paper I have I have pictures from my paper so I'm going to use those so we
나는 내 용지에서 사진이있는 종이 그래서 나는 그 정도 사용하려고 해요 우리
are feeding a commission and omission to accomplish on your network and then
다음 네트워크에서 수행하고 수수료 및 누락을 먹이
you'll see that this phone models actually just made up of two modules
당신이 휴대 전화 모델은 실제로 단지 두 개의 모듈로 구성된 것을 확인할 수 있습니다
there's the comment that is doing the processing of the image and their
이미지와 자신의 처리를하고있다 코멘트가있다
current debt which will be very which is very good with modeling sequences as so
그래서 같은 모델링 시퀀스와 아주 좋은 것입니다 매우 될 것입니다 현재 부채
if you remember my analogy from the very beginning of the course where this is
이 어디 있는지 과정의 처음부터 나의 비유를 기억한다면
kinda like playing with Lego blocks we're going to take those two modules
좀 레고 블록과 재생처럼 우리는 그 두 개의 모듈을거야
and stick them together that corresponds to the arrow in between and so what
사이 그래서 무엇을의 화살표에 해당하는 함께 스틱
we're doing effectively here is where conditioning this RNN generative model
우리가 효과적으로 여기서하고있는 것은 어디 조절이 RNN 생식 모델
or not just telling its sample text at random but we're conditioning that
아니면 그냥 무작위로 그 샘플 텍스트를 이야기하지만 우리는 에어컨 아니에요 그
generate process by the upper to come ashore network and I'll show you exactly
네트워크 해변 와서 상단으로 프로세스를 생성하고 난 당신을 정확하게 보여주지
how that looks like so suppose I'm going to show you what the forward pass on
그 모습 어떻게 그래서 앞으로가 통과 무엇을 보여 드리겠습니다 가정
your own that is so suppose we have a test image and we're trying to describe
자신의 우리가 테스트 이미지를 가지고 우리가 설명하려는 생각된다
it with a sequence of words so the way this model with process the images US
프로세스 방법 이렇게 단어의 시퀀스가​​ 모델 화상을 US
policy which take that any plugin to accomplish on your left work in this
어떤 플러그인이에서 왼쪽 작업을 수행하는 것을 가지고 정책
case is a VG nett so we go through a whole bunch of comics pool and so on
우리가에 만화의 모두 통과 수영장, 그래서 경우는 VG 정가입니다
until we arrived at the end
우리는 단부에 도달 할 때까지
normally at the end we have this automatic classifier which is giving you
일반적으로 마지막에 우리는 당신을주고있다이 자동 분류가
a profit distribution over say 1000 categories of images in this case we're
이익 분배를 통해 우리가있어이 경우 이미지 1000 카테고리 말
going to actually get rid of that classifier and instead we're going to
실제로 분류 없애가는 대신에 우리가 갈거야
redirect representation at the top of the coalition member into the recurrent
재발에 연합 부재의 상단에있는 표현을 리디렉션
neural network so we begin to generation of the Arnon with a special
신경 네트워크는 그래​​서 우리는 특정 함께 아르 논의 생성에 시작
art vector so the impetus are nonetheless I think 300 emotional and
자극이 내가 생각 그럼에도 불구하고 그래서 예술 벡터 (300), 정서적,
this is a special three hundred emotional victory that we always plug
이것은 우리가 항상 플러그 특별한 삼백 감정적 인 승리입니다
into the first iteration tells me that this is the beginning of the sequence
첫 번째 반복이 나에게 이야기에이 시퀀스의 시작입니다
and then we're going to perform the recurrence formula that I shown you
그리고, 우리는 당신을 나타낸 재발 수식을 수행 할거야
before for recurrent neural network normally we computed this recurrence
재발 성 신경 네트워크의 전에 일반적으로 우리는이 재발 계산
which we've solidarity where we compute WSH time sex but whhhy and now we want
우리는 WSH 시간 섹스를 계산하지만 whhhy 지금 우리가 원하는 위치에있는 우리가했습니다 연대
to additionally conditioned as recurrent neural network not only on the current
또한 현재에뿐만 아니라 재발 성 신경 네트워크로 조절합니다
input and current in a state which we must like 20 so that term goes away at
우리가 20을 좋아합니다 상태에서 입력 전류는 그래서 그 용어는 멀리 간다
the first time that but we initially condition just by adding wiht times be
하지만 우리는 처음에 단지 사랑의 시간이 될 추가하여 컨디셔닝 처음으로
and so this is the top of the comment here and we've added interaction and
등이 여기에 주석의 정상이며 우리가 추가 한 상호 작용과
added weight matrix W which tells us how this image information emerges into the
이 이미지 정보가에 나오는 방법을 우리에게 말해 추가 무게 행렬 W
very first time since the recurring role at work now there are many ways to
처음으로 직장에서 재발 역할 때문에 지금 여러 가지 방법이 있습니다
actually play with this recurrence in many ways to actually plug in the image
실제로 실제로 이미지를 연결하는 여러 가지 방법이 재발 플레이
into there are now and this is only one of them and one of the simpler ones
이 지금이 중 하나만 및 간단한 것 중 하나에
perhaps and at the very first time step here in this wine zero vector is the
아마도이 와인에 여기 난생 처음 단계에서 0 벡터 인
distribution over the first word in a sequence so the way this works
이 작동 방식하도록 시퀀스의 첫 번째 단어에 걸쳐 분포
you might imagine for example is you can see that these structures in the mass
예를 들어 당신이 볼 수있다 당신이 상상할 수있는 그 질량이 구조
hat can be recognized by the Coalition network as strong like stuff and then
모자는 다음 연합 네트워크 강한 같은 물건에 의해 인식 될 수있다
through this interaction wiht my condition to hit in state to go into a
내 조건 사랑의이 상호 작용을 통해 들어갈 상태에서 칠
particular state where the probability of the word straw can be slightly higher
단어 짚의 확률이 약간 높을 수있다 특정 상태
right so you might imagine that the strong like textures can influence the
바로 그래서 당신은 강한 같은 텍스처가 영향을 미칠 수 있다는 것을 상상
probability of strong so one of the numbers inside 10 to be higher because
강력한 그래서 번호 중 하나 (10) 내부의 가능성이 있기 때문에 높은 것으로
their structures and so the army from now on has to kind of jungle two tasks
그들의 구조와는 그래서 지금부터 군대는 정글이 작업의 종류에있다
it has to predict the next care and next word in the sequence in this case and it
그것은이 케이스에 시퀀스 내의 다음 치료 및 다음 단어를 예측한다
has to remember the image information so we sent from that sock Max and
그래서 우리는 최대 그 양말로부터 전송 된 화상 정보를 기억하고
supposedly the most likely word that we sampled from that distribution was
아마 우리가 그 분포에서 샘플링 가능성이 가장 높은 단어였다
indeed the word strong we will take strong and we would try to plug it into
참으로 강한 단어 우리는 강한 걸립니다 우리는에 연결하려고 할 것
the recording all that work on the bottom again and so in this case I think
본인은 생각이 경우 다시 그렇게 바닥에 모든 작업을 기록
we're using word level and beddings so the strong strong word is associate with
강한 강한 단어와 연관 그래서 우리는 단어 수준과 침구를 사용하는
a three hundred national Dr we're going to learn to represent the three hundred
삼백 국가 박사는 우리는 삼백를 표현하는 법을 배워야거야
national representation for every single unique jewellery and we plug in those
국가마다 하나의 고유 한 보석에 대한 표현과 우리는 그 플러그
three hundred numbers into the Arnon and forward again to get a description of
삼백 아르 논에 숫자와 설명을 얻기 위해 다시 전달
the second world and sequence inside why one so we get all these properties we
하나는 우리가 이러한 모든 특성을 우리가 얻을 왜 내 두 번째 세계와 순서
sample from it again
그것에서 샘플을 다시
suppose that the word hat is likely now we take hats 400 much older presentation
워드 모자 가능성이 있다고 가정 지금 우리는 모자 400 훨씬 나이 프리젠 테이션을
and get the distribution of it there and then we sample again and we sample until
그리고 거기의 분포를 얻을 후 우리는 다시 샘플링하고 우리는 때까지 샘플
we sample a special and token which is really the period at the end of the
우리는 특별한 샘플 및 진정의 끝에있는 기간 토큰
sentence and that tells us that the arnaz now done generating and at this
문장하고는 arnaz 지금이에서 생성 할 것을 우리에게 알려줍니다
point the army would have described this image as a straw hat period ok so the
군대는 그렇게 확인 밀짚 모자 기간이 이미지를 설명했을 포인트
number of dimensions and his wife picture is a number of words in your
치수와 그의 아내 사진의 수는 단어의 숫자 당신의
vocabulary +1 for the special and token and we are always feeding industry
특수 토큰과 우리가 항상 먹이 산업을위한 어휘 +1
sectors that correspond to different words and a special start talkin and
다른 단어에 해당하는 부문과 얘기 특별한 시작과
then we always just that propagates through the whole thing and a single
우리는 언제나 그 전부 단일 통해 전파
time to nationalize this at random or you can initialize your BG net with free
시간은 무작위로이 국유화하거나 당신은 무료로 BG 그물을 초기화 할 수 있습니다
trade for a minute and then
다음 분을 위해 무역
distributions and then you encode the gradient and then you backed up through
배포판은 다음 그라데이션을 인코딩 한 다음이를 통해 백업
the whole thing as a single model and just trained at all jointly and you get
전체 단일 모델로 것이나 그냥 모든 공동에서 훈련하고 얻을
a caption or image capture lots of questions ok but yes i three hundred
캡션 또는 이미지 캡처 확인 질문을 많이하지만 네 삼백
emotional embeddings they're just independent of the image so every word
감정 묻어은 너무 이미지 모든 단어의 단지 독립적있어
has 300 numbers associated with it so we're going to bankrupt get into it so
그렇게 우리가 그것으로 얻을 파산거야와 관련된 300 번호를 가지고
you initialize it random and then you can back up to get into these better sex
당신은 무작위로 초기화 한 다음이 더 나은 섹스에 들어갈 백업 할 수 있습니다
right so those embeddings will shift around there just a parameter another
그 묻어은 주위 그냥 매개 변수를 다른 이동합니다 오른쪽 그래서
way to think about it is it's to having a one-hop representation for all the
그것에 대해 생각하는 방법은 모두를위한 하나의 홉 표현을 데입니다입니다
words and then you have a giant W matrix where every single
단어는 당신은 거대한 W 매트릭스 곳 하나 하나가
multiplied W with that one hundred plantation and it w has 300 out but size
그 백 농장과 W 곱셈과 승 300 밖으로하지만 크기가
then it's effectively plucking out a single broke up w which and something
효과적으로 하나가 부러 밖으로 따 버릴거야있는 뭔가 w
I'm betting it's kind of a cold front so just think of it if you don't like those
나는 당신이 그 마음에 들지 않는 경우 그래서 그냥 생각이 한랭 전선의 종류의 걸거야
in bed and just think of it as a one-hopper presentation and you can
침대에서 단지 하나의 호퍼 프리젠 테이션으로 생각하고 수행 할 수 있습니다
think of it that way yes the modelers to up at the end token yes in the training
교육에 토큰 네 말에 최대 네 그것의 모델러를 그런 식으로 생각
data the correct sequence that we expect from the art is the first words I can
데이터는 우리가 예술에서 기대하는 올바른 순서는 내가 할 수있는 첫 번째 단어입니다
look forward and so every single training example sort of have a special
기대 때문에 매일 훈련 예 일종의 특별이
and token it go ahead
그리고 진행 토큰
you can wired differently we plugged into every single state it turns out
당신이 유선 수 다르게 우리는 모든 단일 상태로 연결이 밝혀
that actually works worse so it actually works better if you just plug in the
그것은 실제로 당신이 단지에 연결하면 실제로 잘 작동 악화 때문에 작동
very first time step and then the Arnon has to juggle these both tasks that has
시간 단계 최초의 다음 아르 논은이이 두 작업을 저글링하는
to remember about the image what it needs to remember through the art and it
그것은 예술과 그것을 통해 기억 할 필요가 무엇 이미지에 대한 기억
also has to produce all these outfits and somehow it wants to do that there's
또한 이러한 모든 의상을 생산해야하고 어떻게 든 거기에 그렇게하고 싶어
some headway the reasons I can give you after class right that's true
일부는 사실 클래스 직후 나는 당신을 줄 수있는 이유를 전진
a single instance will correspond to an image and a sequence of words and so we
단일 인스턴스는 이미지와 단어의 순서와 우리가 대응합니다
would plug in those words here and we will talk in that image and we shall I
여기에 그 단어를 연결 것이고, I를 우리는 이미지를 이야기하고 우리가하여야한다
come so it's a train time you have all those weren't planning on the bottom of
그래서 와서 당신이 모든 사람들은 바닥에 계획되지 않은 한 기차 시간
the image London and then you unroll this graph and you have your losses in
이미지 런던과 다음이 그래프를 풀다 당신은 당신의 손실을
the background and then you can do batches of images if you're careful and
당신이 조심 있다면 배경이 다음 이미지의 배치를 할 수 있으며,
so if your images they sometimes have different lengths sequences in the
그래서 당신의 이미지를 한 경우에는 때로는 서로 다른 길이의 시퀀스가
training data have to be careful with that because you have to say that ok I'm
당신이 난 것을 확인 말을해야하기 때문에 훈련 데이터는 조심해야
willing to process batches of up to twenty words maybe and then some of
아마 다음의 몇 가지를 최대 스무 단어의 배치를 처리하고자
those sentences will be shorter or longer a need to in your code you know
코드에서 당신이 알고에 그 문장이 짧거나 더 이상 필요가있을 것입니다
worry about that because some some some sentences are longer than others
일부 일부 일부 문장은 다른 사람보다 더 오래 있기 때문에 걱정
we have way too many questions I have stuff to go
우리는 내가 갈 물건이 너무 많은 질문이
yes thank you so that propagate everything completely jointly and two in
그 완전히 공동으로이 모든 것을 전파하도록 네 감사합니다
training so you can pre train with the internet and then you put those words
훈련은 인터넷으로 기차를 미리 할 수​​ 있도록 한 다음 그 단어를 넣어
there but then you just want to train everything jointly and that's a big
이하지만 당신은 공동으로 모든 훈련을 원하고 그 큰이야
advantage actually because we can we can figure out what features to look for in
우리는 우리가 검색 기능을 알아낼 수 있기 때문에 실제로 이점
order to better describe the image that the end so when you train this in
더 좋은 말은 그래서 당신은이 훈련하는 이미지를 설명하기 위해
practice we tried this on the census data sets one of the more common wants
실제로 우리가 인구 조사 자료에이 시도는 일반적인 욕구 중 하나를 설정합니다
is called Microsoft Coco so just to give you an idea of what it looks like it's
마이크로 소프트 코코라고하는 것은, 그래서 그냥 당신이처럼 보이는 무엇의 아이디어를 제공합니다
roughly 800,000 images and five sentence descriptions for each image these were
대략 각 이미지 80 이미지와 다섯 문장의 설명이 있었다
obtained using Amazon Mechanical Turk so you just ask people please give us a
그래서 당신은 단지 사람들에게 아마존 기계 터크를 사용하여 얻은 것은 우리에게주세요
sentence description for an image and your record and end up your data set and
문장 이미지에 대한 설명과 기록 및 데이터 세트를 종료하고
so when you train this model the kinds of results that you can expect or
그래서 당신은 당신이 예상 할 수있는이 모델에게 결과의 종류를 훈련 할 때 또는
roughly what is kinda like this so this is our in describing these images so
약 좀이 같은이 너무 이러한 이미지를 설명하는 우리의 무엇이다
this it says that this is a man in black shirt playing guitar or construction
이 이것이 검은 셔츠 연주 기타 또는 건설 사람이다라고 말한다
worker in Orange City West working on the road or two young girls are playing
도로 또는 두 젊은 여자에 작업 오렌지 시티 웨스트에서 노동자 재생
with Lego toy or boy is doing backflip on a wakeboard and of course that's not
레고 장난감이나 소년 그건 아니에요 웨이크 보드에 물론 공중제비를하고있다
a wakeboard but it's close there are also some very funny failure cases which
웨이크 보드는하지만 매우 재미 실패 사례도 있습니다 가까이있는
I also like to show this is a young boy holding a baseball bat
또한이 야구 방망이를 들고 어린 소년입니다 보여주고 싶은
this is a cat sitting on a couch with the remote control that's a woman
이 고양이는 여자의 원격 제어와 함께 소파에 앉아있다
holding a teddy bear in front of a mirror
거울 앞의 테디 베어를 들고
I'm pretty sure that the texture here probably is what what happened made it
여기 질감은 아마 무슨 일이 것은 그것을 만든 것입니다 확신 해요
think that it's a teddy bear and the last one is a whore standing in the
이 테디 베어가 있다고 생각하고 마지막은 서 창녀입니다
middle of a street road so there's no horse obviously some not sure what
거리 도로의 중간 그래서 분명히 일부 확실하지 아무 말 없다 무엇
happened there so this is just a simplest kind of model that came out
이 나온 모델의 단지 간단한 종류 그래서 거기에 무슨 일이 있었
last year there were many people who try to work on top of these kinds of models
작년 모델의 이러한 종류의 상단에 작업하려고 많은 사람들이 있었다
and make them more complex I just like to give you an idea of 11 level that is
난 그냥 당신에게 11 레벨의 아이디어를 제공하고자 그들을 더 복잡하게
interesting just to get an idea how how people play with this basic architecture
흥미로운 단지 사람들이 기본 아키텍처를 연주하는 방법에 대한 아이디어를 얻을 수
so this is a paper from last year where if you noticed in the current model we
그래서 이것은 현재 모델에서 발견 경우 지난해 종이는 우리
only feed into images single time to time at the beginning and one where you
단지 처음에 시간을 이미지로 한 시간을 공급 한 경우를
can play with this is actually a rowdy recurrent neural network to look back to
이 놀 수있는 것은 실제로 다시 볼 수있는 난폭 한 재발 성 신경 네트워크입니다
the image and reference parts of the image Wireless describing to work does
무선 않는 작동 기술 화상의 화상 및 참조 부
the words such as you're generating every single word you allow the aren't
당신이 허용 등이 모든 단어를 생성하는 등의 단어가 없습니다
actually make a look up next to the image and look for different features of
실제로 이미지 옆 모습을하고 다른 기능을 찾아
what it might want to describe next and you can actually do this in the fully
그것은 다음에 설명 할 수 있습니다 당신은 실제로 완전히에서이 작업을 수행 할 수있는 작업
trainable way so they are not only create these words but also the sides
그들은 단지이 말뿐만 아니라 측면을 생성하지 않도록 학습 가능한 방법
where to look next in the image and so the way this works is not only does the
여기서 이미지에 다음보고하는 등이 작동하는 방식 만을 수행하지 않습니다
Arnon out but you're probably distribution for the next one sequence
아웃 아르 논하지만 당신은 아마 다음 하나의 시퀀스에 대한 분배있어
but this coming that gives you does valium so saying this case we forwarded
하지만 제공이 오는 당신은 발륨은 우리가 전달이 경우 말을 않는
the comment and got a 14 by 14 by 512 by 512 activation volume and at every
512 활성화 부피 (512) (14)에 의해 14를 얻었고에서 모든 및 주석
single time that we don't just admit that distribution but you also emit a
우리는 단지 그 분포를 인정하지 않습니다하지만 당신은 또한을 방출 한 시간
five hundred and twelve dimensional picture that is kinda like a look up key
모양까지 키처럼 좀입니다 오백열둘 차원 사진
of what you want to look for next to the image and so actually I don't think this
당신은 이미지 옆에 그래서 실제로 나는이 생각하지 않습니다 찾기 위해 원하는 것을
is what they did in in this particular paper but this is one way you can wire
그들은이 특별한 종이에 무슨 짓을하지만, 이것은 당신이 연결할 수 있습니다 한 방법입니다
something like this up and saw this picture is emitted from the Arnon just
이 위로이 사진을보고 뭔가는 아르 논에서 방출되는 단지
like it's just predicted using some weights and then this picture can be dot
그냥 약간의 무게와 다음이 그림은 점 수를 사용하여 예측처럼
product and with all these 14 by 14 locations so we do all these dot product
제품이 모든 (14) (14)에 의해 위치가 그래서 우리는 이러한 모든 점 제품을 함께
and we achieved our we compute basically 14 by 14 compatibility now and then we
우리는 우리가 지금 우리가 다음 우리 (14)의 호환성에 의해 기본적으로 14 계산 달성
put a soft max on this so basically we normalize all this so that it's all you
그것은 모두 당신의 있도록 그래서 기본적으로 우리는이 모든 것을 정상화 이것에 부드러운 최대를 넣어
get this what we call in the tension over the image so it's a 14 by 14
이 14 (14)에 의해, 그래서 우리는 이미지를 통해 긴장 부르는이를 얻을 수
probably map over what's interesting for the Arnon right now in the image and
아마 이미지에 지금 아르 논에 대한 흥미로운 내용을 통해지도,
then we use this problem asked to do a weighted sum of these guys with this
우리는이와이 사람의 가중 합을 수행하라는 메시지가이 문제를 사용
saliency
현출
and so this morning can basically a myth of what it thinks is currently
그래서 오늘 아침은 기본적으로는 어떻게 생각하는지의 신화는 현재 수
interesting for it and it goes back and you end up doing a weighted sum of
그것에 대한 흥미가 돌아갑니다 당신은의 가중 합을하고 결국
different kinds of features that the Ellis team wants to look at this point
엘리스 팀이 시점에서보고 싶은 기능의 종류
in time and so for example the island's generating stuff and it might decide
시간 등 섬의 생성 물건, 예를 들어 그것을 결정할 수 있습니다
that ok I'd like to look for something object like now admits a vector file
지금과 같은 객체에 대한보고 싶은 그 확인은 벡터 파일을 인정
numbers of objects like stuff it interacts with cum that's when the
물건 같은 개체의 숫자는이 때의 정액과 상호 작용
comment a commission and maybe some of the object like regions of that coming
위원회 주석 어쩌면 그 지역 같은 개체의 일부는 오는
out of that activation falling like light up and ceiling see map in this
점등 및 천장처럼 떨어지는 정품 인증에서이지도를 참조
4514 irate and then you just end up focusing your attention on that part of
4514 화나게하고 당신은 그 부분에 관심을 집중 결국
the image through this interaction and so you can basically just do lookups
이 상호 작용을 통해 그래서 당신은 기본적으로 그냥 할 수있는 조회 이미지
into the image while you're describing the sentence and so this is something we
이미지에 당신은 문장을 설명하고 그래서이 뭔가 우리 동안
refer to as a soft detention and will actually going to this in a few lectures
부드러운 구금으로 참조 실제로 몇 강연이가는 것
so we're going to cover things like this where the army can actually haven't
그래서 우리는 군대가 실제로하지 않은 수있는이 같은 일을 다루려고
selective attention over its imports as processing the input and that's so I
선택적 입력을 처리하는 등의 수입을 통해 관심과 그 그래서 I
just want to bring it up roughly an hour just to give you a preview of what that
그냥 당신에게 그 무엇의 미리보기를 제공하기 위해 약 한 시간 그것을 가지고 싶어
looks like okay now if we want to make our lives more complex one of the ways
우리가 중 한 가지 방법으로 우리의 삶을 더 복잡하게하려면 이제 괜찮아 보이는
we can do that is to stack them up in layers so this gives you you know more
이 당신을 제공합니다, 그래서 우리가 그 층을 쌓아하는 것입니다 할 수있는 당신이 더 많은 것을 알고
deep stuff usually works better so the way we start this up one of the ways at
깊은 물건은 일반적으로 더 나은 우리가에 가지 방법 중 하나를이를 시작하는 방법을 작동
least you can stack recurrent neural networks and there's many ways but this
적어도 당신은 재발 성 신경 네트워크를 쌓을 수 많은 방법이있다 그러나이
is just one of them that people use in practice as you can
사람들이 당신이 할 수 실제로 사용하는 것이 바로 그 중 하나입니다
straight up just plug harness into each other so the impetus for one Arnon is
똑바로 그냥 서로 그렇게 한 아르 논에 대한 자극이에 하네스를 연결
the director of the State picture of the previous on and so this image we have
우리가 이전에 주 사진의 디렉터 등이 이미지
the time axis going horizontally and then going upwards we have different
시간 축이 수평으로 이동 한 다음 우리가 다른이 위쪽으로가는
ordinance and so in this particular image there are three separate recurrent
이 특정 이미지의 의식 등 세 가지 별도의 재발이 있습니다
neural networks each with their own set of weights and these are colonel that
신경 네트워크는 무게의 자신의 세트와 각각이 대령이다 그
works I just feed into each other and so this is always train jointly there's no
난 그냥 서로 먹이를하지 그래서이 항상 공동으로 더 거기에 훈련되어 작동합니다
train first won second term one that's all just a single competition growth of
기차는 먼저 모든 단지 하나의 경쟁 성장의 두 번째 임기 하나 원
a backdrop to get through this recurrence formula to top it
배경으로는 상단이 재발 식을 통해 얻을 수
ivory britain it's likely to make it more general rule still we're still
상아 영국은 여전히​​ 우리는 여전히있어 더 일반적인 규칙을 만들 가능성이 높습니다
doing the exact same thing is we didn't have the same formula we're taking a
똑같은 일을하면 우리는 우리가 복용하고있는 같은 공식을하지 않았다된다
lecture from below and below in depth and effective from before in time we're
우린 시간 전에에서 아래 아래 깊이와 효과에서 강의
cutting them and putting them supporting them through this w transformation and a
를 절단하고 퍼팅이 w 변환과를 통해 지원
smashing the 10 each
스매싱 10 각
so if you remember if you are slightly confused about this there's there was a
당신이 이것에 대해 약간 혼란스러워하는 경우에 당신이 기억한다면, 그래서 거기있다
WRX H times X plus whah times H you can rewrite this is a concatenation of exxon
WRX H 시간의 X 플러스 당신이 다시 작성할 수 있습니다 whah 시간의 H는 엑손의 연결입니다
H multiplied by a single matrix right so it's as if I stick tacks nation to a
하나의 행렬 곱 H 바로 그래서 난에 침을 국가 스틱 것처럼
single column vector and then I have this w matrix where basically what ends
기본적으로 무슨 일이 끝나는 다음 하나의 열 벡터와 나는이 w 행렬이
up happening is that your WX ages the first part of this matrix and WH
최대 일어나고 당신의 WX 연령이 행렬과 WH의 첫 번째 부분
nation's second part of your matrix and so this kind of formula can be written
미국에서 두 번째로 당신의 매트릭스의 일부 등 식의이 종류는 기록 될 수있다
into formula where you stack with your inputs and you have a single W
식으로 당신은 당신의 입력을 쌓아 단일 W가 어디
transformation so the same formula so that's how we can stop these are
변환은 같은 식 있도록 그래서 우리가이는 중지 할 수 있습니다 방법
announced and then there now indexed by both time and by later at which they
두 시간 색인되는 이후로 지금 다음이 발표하고
occur now one way we can also make these more complex is not shared by stacking
우리는 또한이 더 복잡한이 적층 공유되지 수 있습니다 지금은 한 방향으로 발생
them but actually using a slightly better recurrence formula so right now
그들을 실제로 그렇게 지금 약간 더 반복 공식을 사용하여
so far we've seen as very simple recurrence formula for the return to
지금까지 우리는 복귀에 대한 매우 간단한 재발 수식으로 보았다
work in practice you will actually rarely ever use formula like this and
실제로 작품은 실제로 거의 지금과 같은 공식을 사용하고
basic network is very rarely used instead you'll use what we call it an
기본 네트워크는 매우 드물게 우리가 그것에게 부르는 사용합니다 대신 사용되지 않습니다
LSD and our long short term memory so this is basically used in all the papers
LSD와 오랜 단기 기억은 그래서 이것은 기본적으로 모든 서류에 사용된다
now so this is the formula would be using also your project if you were to
지금이 공식은 당신이 인 경우도 프로젝트를 사용하는 것입니다
use are currently works but I'd like you to notice at this point is everything is
사용이 현재 작동하지만 나는이 시점에서 주목하고 싶은 모든입니다
exactly the same as with an arlen it's just that the recurrence formula has a
동일은 알렌과 마찬가지로이 재발 수식은이 단지의
slightly more complex function ok we're still taking the picture from the low
약간 더 복잡한 기능을 확인 우리는 여전히 낮은에서 사진을 촬영하고
and depth like your input from before in time the previous an estate were
그리고 이전의 시간에 입력 같은 깊이 이전 재산이었다
contacting them putting them through aww transport but now we have this more
연락 그들 앗 전송을 통해 이르렀 그러나 지금 우리는이 더이
complexity and how we actually achieve the New Haven state at this point in
복잡성과 방법을 우리가 실제로이 지점에서 뉴 헤이븐 상태를 달성
time so we're just being a slightly more complex and how to combine defector from
시간은 그래서 우리는 단지 약간 더 복잡한되고있어 방법에서 북한 이탈 주민을 결합
below and before to actually perform an update on heading state just a more
아래 실제로 단지 더 상태를 제목에 업데이트를 수행하기 전에
complex formula so we'll go into some details of exactly what motivates this
이 동기를 부여 정확히 복잡한 공식은 그래서 우리는 몇 가지 세부 사항에 갈거야
formula and why it might be a better idea to actually use in Austin
공식 이유는 실제로 오스틴에서 사용할 수있는 더 좋은 생각이 될 수 있습니다
and it makes sense trust me we'll go through it just right now so if you
그리고 우리가 지금 당장 그것을 통해 갈거야 의미가 나를 신뢰하게 그렇다면 당신
block 4 p.m. some online video or you go to Google Images you'll find diagrams
오후 4시 일부 온라인 비디오를 차단하거나 Google 이미지는 다이어그램을 찾을 수 있습니다로 이동
like this which is really not helping I think anyone the first time I saw him
정말 도움이되지 않는이처럼 사람에게 내가 그를 처음봤을 때 생각
being really scared like this one really scared he was really sure what's going
이 사람이 정말 그가 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 정말 확신했다 겁처럼 정말 무서워되고
on I understand Ellis teams and I still don't know what these two diagrams are
나는 엘리스 팀을 이해하고 난 여전히이 두 다이어그램이 무엇인지 모르는에
so ok so I'm going to try to break down the list and it's kind of a tricky thing
나는 목록을 파괴하려고하는거야하고 ​​까다로운 물건의 종류, 그래서 그렇게 확인
to put into a diagram you really have to kind of step through it so lecture
그것을 통해 단계의 종류 당신이 정말로이 도면에 강의 있도록 넣어
format is perfect for no steam ok so here we have the US equations and I'm
형식은 우리가 미국의 방정식이 있고 난 그래서 여기에없는 스팀 확인을 위해 완벽하다
going to focus on the first part here on the top where we take these two vectors
우리는이 두 벡터를 가지고 위치를 상단에 여기에 첫 번째 부분에 초점을 맞출 것
from below and from before so X and HHS our previous in a state an accident but
아래로부터의 상태에서 이렇게 X와 HHS 이전 전에 사고 있지만,
we met them through that transformation W and now if both Jackson href size and
우리는 변환 W를 통해 지금 모두 잭슨 href가 크기 경우를 만났다
so there's a number send them we're going to end up producing for any
그래서 우리는 어떤을 위해 생산 끝날거야 숫자를 보낼있다
numbers ok through this w matrix which was put forward by 21 so we have these
(21)에 의해 제시되었다이 w 매트릭스를 통해 확인 번호는 그래서 우리는 이러한이
four and dimensional vectors I F oMG they're short for input for get out but
그들이 입력 짧은 것 OMG 경우 사 및 차원 벡터 나가뿐만
and G I'm not sure what that's just you and so the ISI no go through signaled
그리고 G는 나는 당신과 그렇게 ISI없이 신호를 통과 단지를 무엇 확실하지 않다
gates and G go straight tenants gate now the way this way this actually works the
게이트 및 G는 방법에게 지금이 실제로 작동이 길을 똑바로 세입자 게이트로 이동
best way to think about it is one thing I forgot to mention actually in the
그것에 대해 생각하는 가장 좋은 방법은 내가 깜빡 한 가지가 실제로 언급하는 것입니다
previous slide is normally require no network to says the single HVAC tried
이전 슬라이드는 일반적으로 하나의 HVAC 시도 말합니다 할 네트워크를 필요로하지 않습니다
every single time stopped and asked him actually has two vectors that every
매번 중지하고 그에게 물었다 실제로 두 벡터 모든이
single time and thus we call see the cell state vector so that every single
한 시간 때문에 우리는 세포 상태 벡터를 참조 전화를 매도록
time step we have both agency in peril and and see vector here as shown in
시간 단계는 우리가 위험에 두 기관이 있고 그리고에서와 같이 여기 벡터를 참조하십시오
yellow so we basically have two vectors every single point in space here and
노란색 그래서 우리는 기본적으로 두 벡터 여기 공간에있는 모든 단일 지점을 가지고
what they're doing is they're basically operating over this cell state so
그들이하는 일은 그들이 기본적 그래서이 셀 상태에서 작동하고있다
depending on what's before you and below you and that is your context you end up
전에 당신 아래의 내용에 따라 해당 사용자 컨텍스트 당신은 결국
operating over the cell state with these
이들과 함께 세포 상태에서 작동
and Ong elements and new way to think about it is I'm going to go through a
그리고 옹 요소와 그것에 대해 생각하는 새로운 방법 내가 통해 갈거야된다
lot of this way to think about this is I N O as just binary either 0 or 1 we want
이 0 또는 1 우리가 원하는 I NO처럼 이진 않습니다에 대해이 방법을 많이 생각합니다
them to be we want them to have an interpretation of the gate like to think
그들에게 우리가 그들을 게이트의 해석이 생각하고 싶다 갖고 싶어 할 수
of it as heroes are ones we of course make them later signals because we want
영웅이 그들이다 그것의로 우리는 물론 우리가 원하기 때문에 그들에게 이상 신호를 만들
this to be differentiable so that we can back propagate through everything but
우리는하지만, 모든 것을 통해 전파 백업 할 수 있도록이 미분 될 수 있습니다
just think of Ino as just binary things that were computing base in our context
우리의 상황에 기반을 계산 한 바로 진 것들로 이노 생각
and then what this from always doing here see you can see that based on what
항상 여기서 뭘에서이 참조 다음 당신은 무엇을 기준으로 그를 볼 수있는
these gates are and what Diaz we're going to end up dating this see value
이 문은 다음과 디아즈 우리는이 페이지의 값을 데이트 끝날거야 무슨
and in particular this episode to forget gate that will be used to shut a tus
특히이 에피소드는 TUS을 종료하는 데 사용됩니다 게이트를 잊지
reset some of the cells 20 solar cells are best thought of as shelters and
(20) 태양 전지 등의 보호소 가장 생각되는 세포들을 재설정
these counters basically we can either recent than 20 with us this interaction
우리와 함께 (20)이 상호 작용보다 기본적으로 우리가 할 수있는 하나 최근 이러한 카운터
this is an element of multiplication their laser pointer is running out of
이것은 자신의 레이저 포인터가 부족합니다 곱셈의 요소입니다
battery so
배터리 때문에
interaction 0 then you can see that will zero out the cell so we can reset the
상호 작용 0 당신은 우리가를 재설정 할 수 있도록 그 셀을 제로 것이다 볼 수 있습니다
counter and then we can also add to a counter so we can add through this
카운터 그리고 우리는 또한 우리는이를 통해 추가 할 수있는 카운터에 추가 할 수 있습니다
interaction I times G and since I S between 11 and G is between negative one
상호 작용 I 번 G와 11 사이와 G는 부정적 일 사이이기 때문에
in 10 basically adding a number between one and 12 every cell so that every
(10)에 기본적으로 한 12 매 있도록 모든 세포 사이의 숫자를 추가
single time step we have these counters in all the cells we can reset these
우리는이를 재설정 할 수있는 모든 세포에서 이러한 카운터를 하나의 시간 단계
countries 2012 forget Kate or we can choose to add a number between one and
국가 2012 케이트를 잊어 버렸거나 우리는 하나 사이의 숫자를 추가 할 수 있습니다
12 every single cell oK so that's how we performed the cell update and then the
12 그래서 확인을 하나 하나 셀은 우리가 다음 셀 업데이트 및 수행 방법
head an update ends up being a squashed cell so 10 HFC squashed cell that is
업데이트가 찌그러 세포 그렇게 10 HFC는 셀을 숙청되고 끝 머리
modulated by this update so only some of the cell state and up leaking into the
그렇게 만 셀 상태의 일부와 위로로 누출이 업데이트에 의해 변조
hidden state is modulated by this vector oh so we only choose to reveal some of
숨겨진 상태가이 벡터에 의해 변조 오 그래서 우리는 단지의 일부를 공개 선택
the cells into the hen state and learnable way there are several things
암탉 상태와 학습 가능 방법으로 세포는 몇 가지가있다
to to kind of highlight here one maybe most confusing part here is that we're
에 하이라이트의 종류 여기에 아마 여기에 가장 혼란스러운 부분에 우리가 걸이다
adding a number between one and one with I times D here but that's kind of
여기에 D I 배 하나 하나 사이의 숫자를 추가하지만 가지의
confusing because if we only had a G there instead then jeez already between
우리는 단지 거기 G가 있다면 대신 다음 이미 사이에 이름 : Jeez 때문에 혼란
8 11 so why do we need I times G what does that actually giving us when all we
8 11 왜 우리는 내가 여러 번 G 무엇을하지 실제로 우리가 제공하는 모든 필요합니까 우리
want is to implement a sea by
원하는에 의해 바다를 구현하는 것입니다
a number between one and one and so that's kind of my castle part about the
하나 하나 사이의 숫자는 그래서는 대한 내 성 부품의 종류의
last time I think one answer is that if you think about the G it's a function of
마지막으로 내가 한 대답은 당신이 G에 대해 생각하면 그것의 기능 있다고 생각합니다
its a linear function of your context no one has to laser printer by chance right
당신의 문맥의 선형 함수는 하나의 기회가 오른쪽으로 레이저 프린터가 없습니다
ok so G as a function of your Geo 310 age ok so G is a linear function of your
확인 그래서 G는 G 그래서 확인을 지역 310 세의 함수의 선형 함수로
previous contacts squashed by 10 h and so if we were adding just jeans that if
우리가 청바지를 추가 한 경우 10 시간 등에 의해 숙청 이전에 접촉하는 경우
I time she then that would be kind of like a very simple function so by adding
추가하여, 그래서 나는 시간 그녀는 그 종류의 매우 간단한 함수 같은 것
this I and then having a multiplicative interaction you're actually getting more
이 난 후 실제로 더 있어요 곱셈 상호 작용을 갖는
richer function that you can actually expressed in terms of what we're adding
실제로 우리가 추가하는 것을 표현 할 수 있습니다 풍부한 기능
torso state as a function of the previous tests and another way to think
이전 테스트의 기능을 생각하는 또 다른 방법으로 상태를 몸통
about this is that would basically decoupling these two concepts of how
이 약이 기본적으로 방법이 두 개념을 분리하는 것
much do we want to add to a cell state which is G and then do we want to
많은 우리가 G 인 셀 상태로 추가 싶어하고 우리가 원하는 수행
address all state which is so I is likely we actually what this operation
나는 우리가 실제로 무엇을이 조작 가능성이 있으므로 모든 상태를 해결
to go through and genius what we want to by decoupling these two that also may be
또한 될 수 있음이 두 디커플링에 의해 통해 천재 우리가 원하는 이동
dynamically has some nice properties in terms of how this all steam trains but
동적 측면에서 몇 가지 좋은 특성을 가지고 어떻게이 모든 증기 기차하지만,
we just end up that's like the Austin formulas and I'm going to actually go
우리는 단지 그 오스틴 공식처럼 결국 나는 실제로 갈거야
through this in more detail as well
자세한 세부 사항에서이뿐만 아니라 통해
ok so think about this as cell C flowing through and now the first interaction
확인 상기 제 1 상호 작용 이제 셀 C가 흐르는으로 이것에 대해 생각하고
here is the DOTC so efforts in a bit of a sigmoid of that and so economically
여기 그래서 경제적으로 그 시그 모이 약간의 DOTC 그렇게 노력하다
gating yourselves with multiplicative interaction so if f is zero you will
곱셈의 상호 작용으로 자신을 게이팅 F 제로는 것입니다 그래서 만약
shut off the cell and reset the counter the cytology part is basically giving
셀을 차단하고 세포학 부분이 기본적으로 제공되는 카운터를 재설정
you a comp is basically adding to the sole state and then the sub-state leaks
당신은 완은 기본적으로 하위 상태 누수가 유일한 상태로 추가하고있다
into the hill state but only through a 10 h and then that gets gated by so the
언덕 상태로하지만 너무 의해 문이 가도록 한 후 10 시간 통해
only electric and decide which parts with some state to actually reveal into
전기 만 결정 사실로 밝혀 몇 가지 상태에있는 부품
the hidden didn't sell and then you'll notice that this interstate not only
매각하지 않았다 숨겨진 그리고 당신은 알 수가이 고속도로뿐만 아니라,
goes to the next iteration of the STM but it also actually closed up to a
STM의 다음 반복으로 이동뿐만 아니라 실제로까지 폐쇄
higher layers because this is the head of state doctrine that we actually end
상위 계층이 우리가 실제로 종료 상태 교리의 머리이기 때문에
up looking into teams above us or them goes into a prediction
까지 우리 위에 팀으로보고하거나이 예측에 간다
and so when you unroll this basically the way it looks like it's kind of like
이 기본적으로 방법을 풀다 때 그래서 그것이 가지처럼 보이는
this which now I have a confusing diagram of my own thats I guess we ended
지금은 내 자신 그게 전부의 혼란도를 가지고있는이 나는 우리가 끝난 것 같아요
up with but you get your input vectors from below you have your own state from
그러나 아래에서 입력 벡터를 얻을 수와 최대 당신은 당신의 자신의 상태에서이
determine your gates fije know they're all in dimensional vectors and then the
그들은 다음 차원 벡터 및 모든 거 알아 fije 네 성문을 결정
end of modulating how you operate over the cell state and the cell state can
는 셀 상태에서 동작하고, 셀의 상태가 변조 방법을 종료
once you actually we set some countries and once you add numbers between one and
당신이 한 번 실제로 우리는 일부 국가를 설정하고 하나 사이에 번호를 추가하면
12 your country's the cell state leaks out some of it leaks out in a learnable
(12) 국가의 셀 상태는 그것의 일부는 학습 가능에서 누수 밖으로 누출
way and then it can either go up to the prediction or can go to the next
방법 및 다음 중 하나를 예측까지 갈 수 또는 다음에 갈 수 있습니다
iteration of the US team going forward and so that's the so this looks ugly so
미국 팀의 반복은 향후 그래서 그게 그렇게이 그렇게 추한 모습입니다
we're going to so the question is probably in your mind is why did we go
문제는 당신의 마음에 아마 그래서 우리는 거 야 우리가 간다 않은 이유입니다
through all of this there something why does this look at this particular way I
이 특별한 방법 I에서이 Look을 수행하는 이유가 뭔가의 모든 통해
should like to know that this point that there are many various to analyst at
알고 싶어한다 분석가 많은 다양한 있다는 것을이 시점이
this point but by the end of lecture people play a lot with these equations
이 시점하지만 강의 사람들의 말은 이런 식으로 많이 연주
and we've kind of converged on this as being like a reasonable thing but
우리는 종류의 합리적인 것 같은 것으로이에 수렴했지만
there's many little tweaks you can make to this that actually doesn't
당신이 실제로하지 않는이에 수 많은 작은 비틀기가있다
deteriorate the performance by a lot you can remove some of those gates like
당신 같은 사람들 게이트의 일부를 제거 할 수 있습니다 많은하여 성능을 저하
maybe the implicate and so on
아마 연루 등
you can turns out that the stench of see that can be a sea and it works just fine
당신은 할 수의 악취가이 바다가 될 수 볼 밝혀 그것을 잘 작동합니다
normally but with a tender age of seats were slightly better sometimes and I
일반적으로하지만 좌석의 어린 나이로 때로는 약간 더 있었다 I
don't think we have a very good reasons for why and CSI end up with a bit of a
우리는 CSI가의 비트와 함께 결국 왜를위한 아주 좋은 이유가 생각하지 않습니다
monster but I think it actually kinda makes sense in terms of Justice counters
괴물하지만 실제로 좀 법무부 카운터의 측면에서 의미가 생각
that can be reset to zero or you can add small numbers between one and 12 them
그 0으로 재설정 할 수 있습니다 또는 당신은 하나 (12)을 사이에 작은 숫자를 추가 할 수 있습니다
and so it's kind of like a nice actually relatively simple now to understand
지금은 좋은 실제로 비교적 단순한 이해하는 것처럼 그렇게는 가지이다
exactly why this is much better than our own and we have to go to a slightly
이것은 우리 자신보다 훨씬 더 그리고 우리는 약간에 가야 정확하게 이유
different picture to draw the distinction so the recurrent neural
다른 그림은 재발 성 신경 있도록 구별을 그립니다
network that has some state vector right and you're operating over it and you're
어떤 상태 벡터 권리가 네트워크 당신은 그것을 통해 운영하고 있고이있어
completely transforming into through this recurrence formula and so you end
완전히이 재발 식을 통해로 변신 그래서 당신은 종료
up changing your state vector from time to time stuff you'll notice that the US
시간 물건 시간에서 상태 벡터를 변경까지 당신은 미국 것을 알 수 있습니다
team instead has the cell States flowing through and what we're doing effectively
팀 대신 셀 미국이 흐르는 우리가 효과적으로 무슨 일을하고있다
as we're looking at the cells and some of it leaks into the head of state to
우리는 세포에서 찾고 그것의 일부는 국가의 머리에 누수로
state for deciding how to operate over the cell and if you forget gains then we
우리가 이득을 다음 잊어 버린 경우 셀에서 동작하는 방법을 결정하는 상태
end up basically just tweaking the cell by
기본적으로 그냥하여 셀을 조정 끝
active interaction here so so there's some stuff that looked at as a function
함수로 쳐다 보면서 몇 가지 물건이 그래서 그래서 여기 활성 상호 작용
of the cell state and then whatever it is we end up changing the soul state
우리는 영혼의 상태를 변경 결국 그것이 무엇이든 셀 상태의 다음
instead of just transforming it right away so it's an additive instead of a
대신 바로이 첨가제는 대신, 그래서 그것을 변환의
transformative
변형
interaction or something like that now this is actually remind you of something
그런 상호 작용이나 뭐 이제이 실제로 뭔가 당신을 생각 나게한다
that we've already covered in the class with this in mind you that's right yeah
우리가 이미 염두에두고 클래스에 적용되었음을 그, 그래 맞아
so in fact like this is basically the same thing as be solid resonates so
그래서이 같은 사실은 고체와 같은 일이 이렇게 기본적으로 직렬 공진입니다
normally with a calm that we're transforming representation resident has
일반적으로 우리가 표현 거주자가 변화하고 진정으로
these skip connections here and you'll see that basically residents have this
여기에이 스킵 연결 및 당신은 기본적으로 주민들이를 볼 수 있습니다
additive interaction so we have this X here now we do some computation based on
우리가 지금 여기이 X이 때문에 첨가제의 상호 작용 우리는 약간의 계산에 기초 않는다
sex and then we have an additive interaction with acts and so that's the
다음 섹스 그리고 우리는 행위와 첨가제의 상호 작용을 가지고 있고 그래서는이다
basic block of residents and that's in fact what happens with an awesome as
같은 멋진로 발생하는 기본 주민들의 블록과 그 사실의
well we have these interactions we're here and the ex is your cell and we go
물론 우리는 우리가 여기있어 이러한 상호 작용을 가지고 전은 세포이며, 우리가 간다
off with you some function and then we choose to add to this cell state but the
다음 몇 가지 기능은 당신과 떨어져 우리는이 세포 상태 만에 추가 할 수
LSD and unlike residents have also please forget dates that were adding
LSD와는 달리 주민들은 또한 추가 된 날짜를 잊지하시기 바랍니다있다
these forget case-control choose to shut off some parts of the signal as well but
이뿐만 아니라 신호의 일부를 차단하도록 선택할 경우 제어를 잊지 있지만,
otherwise it looks very much like a president so I think it's kind of
그렇지 않으면 나는 그것이 가지 생각 때문에 대통령처럼 매우 보인다
interesting that were converging on very similar kind of looking architecture
보고 아키텍처와 매우 유사 종류에 수렴하고 그 재미
that works both income that's end in recurrent neural networks where it seems
보인다 곳은 재발 성 신경 네트워크에서 끝의 두 소득을 작동
like dynamically somehow it's much nicer to actually have these additive
같은 동적으로 어떻게 든 실제로 이러한 첨가제를 가지고 훨씬 좋네요이다
interactions that allow you to actually that propagate much more effectively so
당신이 실제로 훨씬 더 효과적으로 그렇게 전파 할 수 있도록 상호 작용
to that point
그 시점에
think about the the back propagation dynamics between our analysis team
분석 팀 사이의 뒷면 전파 역학에 대해 생각
especially in the US team is very clear that if I inject some gradients and
특히 미국 팀에 좀 그라디언트를 주입하면 매우 명확하고
sometimes that's here so if I inject radiance and let the end of this diagram
가끔 내가 생기를 주입하고이 그림의 끝을 보자, 그래서 만약 여기에
then these plus interactions are just like ingredients superhighway here right
다음이 플러스 상호 작용은 바로 여기 그냥 재료 고속도로처럼
like these videos will just flow through all the tabs addition interactions right
이 동영상은 모든 탭 추가 상호 작용 오른쪽으로 흐르는 것 같은
because edition distributed equally so if I plugging gradient any point in time
내가 그라데이션 시간의 어느 지점을 연결하는 경우 버전은 동일하므로 분산 때문에
here just going to blow all the way back and then of course the gradient also
여기에 단지 물론 그라데이션도 다시 모든 방법을 날려 가고
flows through these acts and they end up contributing their ingredients into the
이러한 행위를 통해 흘러 그들이에 자신의 재료를 기여 결국
reading to flow but you'll never end up with what we refer to with our intense
독서 흐름합니다하지만 당신은 우리가 우리의 강렬한으로 참조 무​​엇으로 끝낼 수 없을거야
problem called vanishing regions where these gradients just died off go to zero
이 그라디언트 그냥 제로로 이동을 사망 어디에 문제가 지역 사라지는라고
as you back propagate through and I'll show an example
당신은 다시 통해 전파 내가 예를 보여 드리겠습니다로
completely off why this happens in a bit sonar now we have this banishing
완전히이 조금 수중 음파 탐지기에서 발생하는 이유 떨어져 지금 우리는이 배니싱이
gradient problem I'll show you why that happens analyst am because of this
나는 당신을 보여줄 것 그라데이션 문제는 이유는이 때문에 애널리스트 오전 발생
superhighway of just editions these gradients of every single time step that
그냥 판의 고속도로 매 시간 단계의 이러한 구배가
we inject into the US team from above
우리는 위의 미국 팀에 주입
just flow through the cells and your ratings don't end up finishing at this
그냥 세포를 통과하고 등급이에서 마무리 결국하지 않습니다
point maybe I take some questions are there questions about what's confusing
어쩌면 내가 몇 가지 질문을 가리 혼란 기능에 대한 질문이 있습니다
here but the last time and then after that I'm going to why arnaz have been in
여기하지만 마지막으로 한 다음 그 후 나는 arnaz가에 있었던 이유에 갈거야
Greensboro
그린 즈 버러
yes 000 vector is that important
예 000 벡터가 중요한 것입니다
turns out that I think that one specifically is not super important so
내가 하나가 특별히 매우 중요 아니라고 생각 밝혀
there's a paper I'm going to show you what else to answer Space Odyssey they
나는 스페이스 오디세이 그들이 대답 할 다른 무엇을 보여 드리겠습니다 종이가있다
really played with this take stuff out but stuff in there there's also like
정말 거기에이 걸릴 물건 아웃하지만 물건을 연주 또한 같은있다
these people connections you can you can add so this cell state here that can be
당신이 그렇게이 셀 상태가 여기에있을 수 추가 할 수 있습니다 사람들의 연결
actually put in with the hidden state better as an input so people really play
사람들이 정말 재생할 수 있도록 실제로 입력으로 더 나은 숨겨진 상태에 넣어
with this architecture and they tried lots of iterations of exactly these
이 아키텍처 그들은 바로 이러한 반복을 많이 시도
equations and what you end up with us almost everything works about equal some
방정식과 거의 모든 약 동일한 일부 작동 당신이 우리와 끝까지
of it we're slightly were sometimes so it's very kind of confusing in this in
그것을 우리는 약간은 매우 가지 혼란이있는, 그래서 때로는 있었다있어
this way to show your paper where they took they treated the DS update
그들은했다 어디 용지를 표시하려면이 방법은 그들이 DS 업데이트를 처리
equations has just been built trees over the update equations and then they did
방정식은 업데이트 방정식을 통해 나무를 내장하고있다 그리고 그들은했다
this like random mutation stuff and they tried all kinds of different grass and
이 같은 무작위 돌연변이 물건과 서로 다른 잔디의 모든 종류의 시도
updates you can have and most of them work about some of them break some of
사용자가 업데이트 할 수 그들 대부분은 그들 중 일부의 일부를 파괴에 대해 작동
them work about the same but nothing like really does much better than
정말보다 훨씬 더 않습니다처럼은 동일하지만 아무것도에 대한 작업
analyst team and the questions are going to why recurrent neural networks have
분석 팀과 질문 재발 성 신경 네트워크가 왜 가고있다
terrible backward flow video also
또한 끔찍한 역류 비디오
showing the vanishing gradients problem in recurrent neural networks with
와 재발 성 신경 네트워크에서 사라지는 그라데이션 문제를 보여주는
respect to all stems so we're showing here as we're looking at a recurrent
모두에 대해 우리가 재발보고있는 것처럼 우리가 여기에 표시하고 줄기
neural network over many periods many time steps and then injecting gradient
많은 기간 많은 시간 단계에 걸쳐 신경망 다음 주입 그라데이션
and say it's a hundred and twenty eighth time step and we're bankrupting
그것은 백 스물여덟번째 시간 단계의 말을 우리는 파산하고
ingredients through the network and we're looking at what is the gradient
네트워크를 통해 재료와 우리는 그라데이션이 무엇인지보고있는
for I think the input type hidden matrix one of the weight matrices at every
용 나는 체중의 입력 타입 숨겨진 매트릭스 하나에 모든 행렬 생각
single time step so remember that to actually get the full update through the
한 시간 간격 때문에 실제로 통해 전체 업데이트를 얻기 위해 그 기억
back we actually adding all those gradients here and so what's what's
다시 우리가 실제로 여기에 모든 그라디언트를 추가하고 그래서 무엇 무엇이다
what's being shown here is that as a backdrop we only inject ingredient at
어떻게 여기에 표시되는 것은 배경으로 우리는 단지에서 성분을 주입하는 것입니다
120th time steps we do backdrop back through time and the strong the slices
우리가 시간과 강한 조각을 통해 배경을 120 시간 단계
of that propagation what you're seeing is that the US team gives you lots of
그 전파의 당신이보고있는 것은 미국 팀이 당신을 많이 준다이다
gradients throughout this backpropagation so there's lots of
많이있다, 그래서이 역 전파에 걸쳐 그라데이션
information that is flowing through this art and just instantly dies off that
단지 바로이 기술을 통해 흐르는되는 정보는 전원 사망
just greedy and we say banishes just just becomes tiny numbers there's no
그냥 욕심 우리는 추방은 그냥 아무 거기에 작은 숫자가된다라고
gradient so in this case I think indication about a time steps are so
내가 단계 그렇게되는 시간에 대해 표시를 생각이 경우 너무 그라데이션
like 10 times steps as all the information that we injected did not
우리가하지 않았다 주입 모든 정보와 10 배 단계 등
flow through the network and you can't learn very long dependencies because all
네트워크를 통해 흘러 모든 때문에 매우 긴 종속성을 배울 수 있습니다
the correlation structure has been just died down there so we'll see why this
우리가 왜이 볼 수 있도록 상관 관계 구조는 아래가 사망 한
happens dynamically in a bit there some comments your channel so funny he's like
조금 동적으로 발생이 채널이 너무 재미 그가처럼 몇 가지 코멘트
YouTube or something
YouTube 또는 뭔가
ok
그래
ok so let's look at very simple example here we have a recurrent neural network
확인 그래서 우리가 재발 성 신경 네트워크가 여기 아주 간단한 예를 살펴 보자
that I'm going to unfold for you in this recurrent neural network I'm not showing
내가 보여주는 아니에요이 재발 성 신경 네트워크에 당신을 위해 전개거야 것을
any inputs we're only have his state updates so wait whaaa church and state
우리가있어 모든 입력은 자신의 상태 업데이트가 너무 whaaa 교회와 대기 상태가
hidden to hit an interaction and I'm going to basically forward a recurrent
상호 작용을 칠 숨겨진 나는 기본적으로 재발을 전달하려고 해요
neural network does it not for some tea time steps here I'm using T-fifty so
신경망 때문에 T-오십를 사용하고 여기에 내가 어떤 차 시간 단계를하지를 않습니다
what I'm doing is WHAS time the previous tenant and stuff and then on top of that
내가 무슨 일을하고있어 WHAS 시간을 그 위에 다음 이전 세입자와 물건과입니다
so this is just a forward pass for ignoring any input vectors coming in is
그래서 이것은 모든 입력 벡터를 무시 들어오는 단지 전진 패스입니다
just WHAS times H threshold WHAS time sage threshold and so on
단지 WHAS 시간 H 임계 값 WHAS 시간 세이 임계 값 등
that's the forward pass and then backward pass here where i'm directing a
그 전진 패스의 다음 뒤로 여기가 연출하고있어 여기서 통과
random gradient here at the last time step so in the 50th time step by
마지막 단계에서 여기에 임의의 기울기에 의해 50 시간 단계에서 매우
injecting gradient which is random and then go backwards and I backed up so
뒤쪽으로 이동 한 후 무작위 및 그라데이션을 주입 나는 그렇게 백업
when you back up through this right you have to back up through here I'm using a
당신은 백업이 권한을 통해 여기 내가 사용하고 있습니다 통해 백업해야 할 때
rather get the backdrop through a wh multiply than 400 W H multiply and so on
오히려 곱셈 등 400 WH보다 곱셈 어를 통해 배경을 얻을
and so the thing to note here is so here I am doing developers brownback
그래서 여기서주의 할 것은 여기에서 매우이다 나는 개발자 브라운 백을하고있는 중이 야
propagate through the relevant just holding anything that where the imports
수입을 어디에서 관련 바로 잡고 아무것도 통해 전파
were less than zero and Here I am dropping the WH times each operation
나는 WH 시간마다 작업을 제로보다 작은 여기서 포기하고 있었다
where we actually multiplied by WH matrix before we do the nonlinearity so
우리가 실제로 WH 행렬 곱 경우 우리는 그렇게 비선형 성을하기 전에
there's something very funky going on when you actually look at what happens
당신이 실제로 무슨 일을 볼 때가는 매우 펑키 뭔가가있다
to these DHS which is the gradient on the NHS as you go backwards through time
당신이 시간을 통해 뒤로 이동으로 NHS의 구배이 DHS에
it has a very kind of funny structure that is very worrying as you look at
당신이 보는 것처럼 매우 걱정입니다 재미있는 구조의 매우 종류가 있습니다
like how this gets chained up in the loop like what we're doing here with
등이 우리가 여기 무슨 일을하는지와 같은 루프에 연결되는 방식
these two time steps
두 시간 간격
zeros yes I think and sometimes that's maybe the outputs the rebels were all
제로 그래 나는 생각하고 가끔 어쩌면 반군이 모든 있었다 출력의
dead and seemed you may have killed it but that's not really the issue of the
죽은 당신을 죽일 수 듯하지만 그건 정말 문제 아니다
more worrying issue is well that would be a show of all but I think one wearing
더 걱정 문제는 그 모든 쇼가 될 것 잘하지만 착용 한 생각
issue that people can easily spot as well as you'll see that we're
사람들이 쉽게 우리가 걸 볼 수 있습니다뿐만 아니라 발견 할 수 있습니다 문제
multiplying by this whah matrix over and over and over again because in the
때문에에 또 다시 이상이 whah 행렬 곱
forward pass we multiply by awhh at every single iteration
앞으로 우리가 매일 반복에 awhh 곱 통과
back propagates through all the hidden states we end up back propagating this
다시 우리가이 전파 결국 모든 숨겨진 상태를 통해 전파
formula wh ich konnte chess and a backrub turns out to actually be that
무형 문화 유산 konnte 체스와 backrub 어 공식은 실제로 것을 밝혀
you take your greeting signaling multiplied by whah matrix and so we end
당신은 whah 행렬 곱 인사말 신호를 가지고 우리는 종료
up the gradient gets multiplied by whah hold it then multiplied by WH official
그라데이션이 whah 유지를 곱한 도착까지 그 다음 WH 관계자를 곱한
did so we end up multiplying by does matrix WH age fifty times and so the
그렇게 우리는 그렇게하지 ​​매트릭스 W​​H 나이 오십 번 곱 결국
issue with this is that the green signal basically two things can happen like if
이 가진 문제는 녹색 신호는 기본적으로 두 가지 경우처럼 일어날 수 있다는 것입니다
you think about working with scalar value supposedly scale is not matrices
당신은 아마 규모 행렬없는 스칼라 값 작업에 대한 생각
if I take a number that's random and then I have a second number and I keep
그때 임의의 번호를 가지고 있다면 두 번째 번호가 나는 유지
multiplying the first number by the second number so again and again and
그래서 또 다시 두 번째 숫자에 의해 첫 번째 숫자를 곱한
again what does that sequence go to their cases right to play with the same
다시 그 순서는 바로 같은 플레이 자신의 경우에 무엇을 이동 않습니다
number either I die or just goes to sleep yet if your second number exactly
번호 하나 내가 죽거나 아직 경우 두 번째 번호를 정확히 절전 모드로 전환
one year so that the only case where you don't actually explode but otherwise
일년 실제로 폭발하지만, 그렇지 않는 경우에만 위치하도록
really bad things are happening either die or we explode and here we have major
정말 나쁜 일이 죽을 중 하나 일어나고 또는 우리는 우리가 큰이 여기 폭발
cities we don't have a single number but in fact it's the same thing happens a
도시 우리는 하나의 번호가없는 있지만, 사실은이 같은 일이 일어난다이다
generalization of it happens in the spectral radius of the WHS major axis
그것의 일반화는 WHS 장축 반경 스펙트럼에서 일어나는
which is the largest eigenvalue of that matrix is greater than one then does
이는 그 행렬의 최대 고유 한 후보다 큰 것이다
radio signal will explode if it's lower than one degree in civil completely died
이 시민은 완전히 사망의 1도 이하의 경우 무선 신호가 폭발
and so basically since dr Tan has this very weird because of this recurrence
그래서 기본적으로 박사 탄 때문에이 재발이 매우 이상한이 있기 때문에
formula we end up at this very just terrible dynamics and it's very unstable
공식 우리는 매우 끔찍 역학에 결국 그리고 그것은 매우 불안정입니다
and just dies or explodes and so in practice the way this was handled was
그냥 그렇게 연습이 처리 된 방법을 폭발하고 또는 사망했다
you can control the exploding gradients one simple hockey as if your greetings
당신은 폭발 그라디언트에게 인사말 마치 하나의 간단한 하키를 제어 할 수 있습니다
exploding you click it
폭발 당신은 그것을 클릭
so people actually do this and practices like a very patchy solution but if
그래서 사람들은 실제로 매우 누덕 누덕 기운 솔루션처럼하지만 경우에이 관행을
you're reading Does above five min Norman Lin clampett 25 element twice or
두 번 다섯 분 노먼 린 크램 펫 (25) 요소 위에합니까을 읽고있는 나
something like that so you can do that is degrading clipping that's how you
당신이 저하되어 클리핑을 수행 할 수 있도록 그런 일이 그 방법을의
address the exploding grading problem and then you're you're recording don't
폭발 등급을 매기는 문제를 해결하고 당신은 당신이 기록하고있어하지 않습니다
explode anymore but the Greens can still vanish in a carnival at work and Ellis
더 이상 폭발 그러나 녹색당은 여전히​​ 직장과 엘리스에서 카니발에서 사라질 수 있습니다
team is very good with the vanishing gradient problem because of these
팀 때문에 이들의 사라지는 그라데이션 문제에 아주 좋은 것입니다
highways of cells that are only change with additive interactions with the
단지와 첨가제의 상호 작용에 따라 변화되는 세포의 고속도로
gradient just blow they never die down if you are if you because you're
당신은 당신이이기 때문에 경우에 당신이 경우 구배는 단지 그들이 아래로 죽지 않을 날려
multiplying by the same age or something like that that's roughly why these are
이러한 이유 대략이다처럼 같은 나이 또는 무언가에 의해 곱
just better dynamically so we always teams and we do do gradient clipping
단지 더 동적으로 우리는 항상 팀 그래서 우리는 그라데이션 클리핑을 수행 할
usually so because the gradients in Dallas team can potentially explode
일반적으로 달라스 팀의 기울기가 잠재적으로 폭발 할 수 있기 때문에
still made they don't usually vanish
여전히 그들은 일반적으로 사라하지 않는했다
recurrent neural networks as well for Ellis teams it's not clear where you
재발 성 신경 네트워크뿐만 아니라에 대한 엘리스 팀은 분명하지 않다 어디를
would plunge in its not clear in this equation like exactly how you would plug
당신이 플러그 것입니다 정확히 같은이 식의 명확하지에 뛰어들 것
into relative and where maybe instead of the May from G much since then attend
상대적으로 어디에 아마 대신 G에서 월의 많은 다음에 참석하기 때문에
huug here but then resells would only grow in a single direction right so
여기 huug하지만 재판매는 바로 이렇게 하나의 방향으로 성장할 것
maybe then you can't actually end up making it smaller so that's not a great
어쩌면 당신은 실제로 좋은 아니에요 작게 있도록 만드는 끝낼 수 없다
idea I suppose you know so there is basically there's no clear way to plug
난 당신이 알고있는 가정 아이디어는 이렇게 연결하는 명확한 방법이 없습니다 기본적으로됩니다
in a row here so yeah one thing I notice that in terms of these superhighways
여기에 행을 너무 좋아 한 것은 나는이 초 고속도로의 측면에서 그 통지
gradients this this viewpoint actually breaks down when you have four get gates
네 개의 얻을 문이있을 때이 그라디언트 이러한 관점은 실제로 고장
because when you have four get Kate's where we can forget some of these acts
네 개의 얻을 때 때문에 케이트의 우리는 이러한 행위의 일부를 잊을 수있는 곳
with the multiplicative interaction then whenever I forget gates turns on and it
내가 문을 잊지 때마다 곱셈 상호 작용은 다음에 그것과 세가와
kills the gradient then of course the backward flow will stop so these super
다음 그라데이션을 죽이고 물론 역류 때문에 이러한 슈퍼 중단됩니다
highways are only kind of true if you don't have any forget gates but if you
당신이없는 경우 고속도로 가지 사실 어느 문을 잊지하지만 당신은 경우
have a forget gave their then it can kill the gradient and so in practice
a는 다음 그라디언트를 죽일 수 그들의줬고, 그래서 실제로 잊지했다
when we play with us teams are we use Austin's I suppose sometimes people when
우리는 우리와 함께 연주 할 때 팀은 우리가 가끔 사람들이 때 가정 오스틴의 사용이다
they initially to forget get to the initializer with a positive bias because
긍정적 인 편견 때문에 함께 초기화에 그들이 처음 잊지 얻을
that by
에 의한
forget to to turn on to me always kind of turned off I suppose in the beginning
나에 설정하는 것을 잊지 항상 종류의 내가 처음에 생각 해제
so in the beginning the green spoke very well and then the US team can learn how
그래서 처음에 녹색 아주 잘 이야기하고 미국 팀은 배울 수있는 방법
to shut them off at once you later on so people play with that bias on that for
그 해당 바이어스 용으로 나중에 사람들이 재생되도록 한 번에 그들을 차단하기
decades sometimes and so the last night here I wanted to mention that cost him
수십 년 때때로 그래서 여기에 지난 밤 나는 그 비용을 언급하고 싶었다
so many people have basically play with this quite a bit so there's a Space
공간이 그래서 많은 사람들은 기본적으로이 꽤 플레이 한
Odyssey paper where they tried various changes to the architecture there's a
그들이 아키텍처로 다양한 변화를 시도 오디세이 용지 거기
paper here that tries to do this search over huge number of potential changes to
잠재적 인 변화의 큰 숫자 이상이 검색을 수행하려고 여기에 종이
the LST equations and they did a large search and they didn't find anything
LST 방정식 그리고 그들은 많은 검색을했고, 그들은 아무것도 찾지 못했습니다
that works substantially better than just analyst am so yeah and then there's
그건 그냥 애널리스트 오전 너무 좋아하고있어보다 실질적으로 더 잘 작동
the GRU which also has a relatively actually popular and I would actually
또한 상대적으로 실제로 인기가 있고 내가 실제로 것 GRU
recommend that you might want to use this drus a change in the Coliseum it
당신이 콜로세움 그것의 변화를 개의 DRU 사용 할 수 있습니다 것이 좋습니다
also has decided to interactions with nice about it is that it's a shorter
그것은 짧은 점이다 대해도 좋은 상호 작용으로 결정했다
smaller formula and it only has a single a tractor doesn't have a Tennessee it
작은 공식과 단지 하나있는 테네시을 갖지 않는 트랙터
only has an H so implementation wise is just nicer to remember just a single had
구현은 현명한 단지 하나가 가진 기억 단지 좋네요 있도록 만 H가
a setback in your forward past two factors as just a smaller simpler thing
단지 작은 간단한 일이 같은 앞으로 과​​거 두 가지 요인에 차질
that seems to have most of the benefits of a nasty but so it's called GRU and it
그 불쾌한의 혜택의 대부분을 갖고있는 것 같아요하지만 그래서는 GRU과라고
almost always works about the coolest and in my experience and so you might
거의 항상 멋진에 대한 내 경험에 작동하고 그래서 당신은 수도
want to use it or you can use the last time they both kinda knew about the same
그것을 사용하려는 또는 당신은 그들이 모두 좀 동일한 대해 알고 마지막 시간을 사용할 수 있습니다
and so somebody is that harness are very nice but the rawr and does not actually
그래서 누군가가 마구는 아주 좋은하지만의 RaWR하고 실제로하지 않는 것입니다
work very well
아주 잘 작동
soyuz US teams are used instead what's nice about them is that weird having
소유즈 미국 팀은 무엇을 그들에 대해 좋은 데요 것은 이상한 갖는 것입니다 대신 사용된다
these additive interactions that allow Greece to play much better and you don't
그리스을 허용 이러한 첨가제의 상호 작용은 매우 잘 재생 당신은하지 않습니다
get a vanishing breed problem we still have to worry a bit about the exploding
사라지는 품종 문제를 얻을 우리는 여전히 폭발에 대해 조금 걱정
feeding problems so it's common to see people clip these women sometimes and I
이 사람들은 때때로 내가이 여자 클립을 참조하는 것이 일반적 그래서 문제를 공급
would say that better simpler architectures are really trying to
더 간단한 구조가 정말하려고하는 말 것
understand how come there's something deeper going on with the connection
연결과 무슨 깊은 거기에 뭔가 오는 방법을 이해
between residents and Ellis teams and there's something deeper about these
주민과 엘리스 팀 사이에 이들에 대해 뭔가 깊은있다
interactions that I think we're not fully understanding yet exactly why that
나는 우리가 아직 정확히 그 이유는 완전히 이해되지 것 같아요 상호 작용
works so well and which parts of it were cool and so I think we need to
그래서 잘 작동하고 어떤 부분은 시원했고, 그래서 우리가 필요하다고 생각
understand both theoretical and empirical in the space and it's a very
공간 이론과 경험을 모두 이해하고 그것은 매우이야
wide open area of research and so so it's
벌리고 연구의 영역과 그래서 그래서
sport 10 but the end of class where they can I i suppose to explode so it's not
스포츠 (10) 그러나 나는 내가 그렇지 않은 그래서 폭발 가정 할 수 클래스의 끝
as clear why they would but you keep injecting gradient into the cell state
명확 왜 것이라고하지만 당신은 세포 상태로 그라데이션을 주입 유지
and so maybe degrading can sometimes get larger
그래서 어쩌면 때때로 큰 얻을 수 있습니다 저하
it's common to collect em but I think not as may be important maybe as an hour
그것은 그들을 수집하는 것이 일반적이지만 중요 할 수 있으므로 한 시간으로 아마 생각
and then I'm not a hundred percent sure about that point but urological basis I
그리고, 나는 그 시점하지만 비뇨기과 기초 I에 대해 확실히 백퍼센트 아니에요
have no idea what's interesting yeah I think we should end up here but I'm
흥미로운 무슨 생각 그래 나는 우리가 여기까지해야한다고 생각하지 않습니다 있지만 난
happy to take your questions here
여기에 질문을 드리겠습니다